Delwath: Okay, this is making me think.
Delwath: Is there any
Delwath: dragon that is resistant to aci-
Wellby: Ooze?
Delwath: Or immune to ooze. Immune to acid damage.
Wellby: Uh, black dragons.
DM: Black dragons and possibly
DM: copper or bronze.
Delwath: I mean... But black dragons also do acid damage.
DM: Yeah. That's, that's the downside to dragons is-
Unknown: Mm
DM: ... they all are resistant to the damage they do.
DM: So if you want to be resistant to...
DM: Which actually,
DM: theoretically is pretty good for Seeker
DM: because you could... Seeker could turn into a dragon resistant to acid damage and then just cast spells instead of-
Unknown: Oh
DM: ... using the breath weapon.
Seeker: That makes sense.
Seeker: So what's a dragon resistant to acid damage?
Delwath: Um, a copper dragon is not only resistant to acid damage, it's immune to acid damage.
Seeker: That's even better.
Delwath: It's only challenge 14, but...
DM: But if you're just gonna be casting spells, that's
DM: better.
Delwath: It, it has a...
Delwath: It can replace one, it has a slowing breath.
Seeker: Like, what are the ooze's minions gonna look like?
Seeker: We just have no idea what we're walking into, as always.
Delwath: I mean, a copper dragon is not crazy.
Unknown: Let's put-
Delwath: Oh, man. An ancient copper dragon is one-
DM: It's CR21
Delwath: ... It's CR21. It's one too high.
Wellby: Yeah.
Seeker: Seeker is, like, not interested in dragon things.
DM: Yeah, Seeker's done the dragon thing and-
Unknown: Yes. Seeker's done
DM: [laughs]
Kenzo: We give you some trav- dragon, uh, trauma bonding, Seeker.
Wellby: Seeker's full name is actually-
Delwath: But, but like, Kenzo had very successful-
DM: Kenzo, it wasn't traumatic at all
Kenzo: ... Oh, I know. Kenzo loved that shit.
Wellby: Novelty Seekers.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah. What's up?
Wellby: No, T- T is short for something.
Wellby: It's a middle name.
Unknown: Novelty Seeker.
Kenzo: [laughs] Um, somebody had, like, a USB-C charger over here.
DM: That, that was mine.
Unknown: I know.
DM: Oh, here. Here.
Delwath: Do you need a USB-C?
DM: My, my computer is fully charged.
Delwath: I also... I have one that I'm not using, if you guys need more.
Kenzo: Yeah, maybe just a half and half to charge random things.
Delwath: Uh, I think I have one.
Seeker: Are any of the dairy products known good, like milks or cream?
DM: All of the dairy products should be known good.
Wellby: The half and half I just opened this morning, if that's relevant.
Unknown: It's the purple one here?
Wellby: Yeah.
Seeker: All right. I'm just trying to maximize my ideas.
Unknown: Ah, right.
Unknown: Do you have a USB-C charger?
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: I might actually use...
Kenzo: No, I'm not.
Kenzo: No, don't worry about it. I'll, I'll worry about it.
Unknown: No big deal.
Unknown: Oh.
Kenzo: Man, this is so awesome.
Kenzo: I love that we do this every year.
Wellby: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unknown: This table.
Unknown: It's really, it's really,
Kenzo: it's super fantastic. Oh, perfect.
Unknown: Thank you.
Unknown: Oh, wow.
Unknown: My fancy little travel charger.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: I got sick of-
DM: It even has a plug
Delwath: ... I got sick of hotel rooms that did not have enough plugs to charge my...
Unknown: Here.
Unknown: Sweet.
Delwath: I mean, a copper dragon, its breath weapon's...
Delwath: It has a slowing breath
DM: which recharges. [package rustling] Its rend does acid damage,
Delwath: but that's... Who cares?
DM: Copper dragon?
Delwath: Copper dragon.
Unknown: Sounds pretty cool.
Unknown: It-
Seeker: Is there anything that's not a copper dragon or not a dragon that is also immune to acid damage?
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: let's see. Could I search [package rustling]
DM: Yeah, you can search for that
Delwath: ... damage immunity acid?
Unknown: Challenge.
Seeker: Oh, like that poison troll or whatever
Wellby: that we trapped one time.
Delwath: Oh, yeah. Is that still in the Mir- or Mirror?
DM: No, the poison troll destroyed...
Unknown: We defeated it.
Unknown: The vampires.
Wellby: We defeated it.
Wellby: The vampires, yeah.
DM: We destroyed the vampires.
Delwath: Um, let's see. A black dragon is also
Delwath: immune to acid.
Kenzo: Eric, did you do this with your mind?
DM: [laughs]
Seeker: I did it unintentionally with my mind.
Delwath: It's, um... The black dragon is not as good as a copper dragon, I don't think.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: let's see. Hold on. I got a filter on.
DM: A leviathan.
Seeker: I'm down for that.
DM: Gigantrian elemental.
Unknown: The le- the leviathan.
DM: Gigantic serpent.
Unknown: From afar.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Immune to acid and poison.
Seeker: Yeah, this is the one.
DM: Your... But your d- your attacks do am- acid damage too.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: But, I mean-
Seeker: I fucking ca- spell cast.
DM: You can cast spells, yeah.
Delwath: And a tidal wave.
Seeker: Has that got a compatible CR?
DM: Yeah, it's CR20. [coughs] Three legendary resistances.
DM: If you take 50 or more cold damage in a single turn, you partially freeze.
Unknown: Hm.
DM: And-
Delwath: It actually has resistance to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing, immunity to acid and poison.
DM: But from non-magical sources.
Delwath: Yeah, that's true. That will be meaningless.
Unknown: Uh, ex-
DM: Oh
Delwath: ... immune to exhaustion, grappled, paralyzed, petrified, poisoned, prone, restrained, and stunned.
Delwath: It's pretty good.
DM: Yeah, that is pretty good.
Delwath: It's like a giant...
Delwath: It's basically a giant water elemental.
DM: Yeah, it's a sea serpent.
Delwath: No, it's like a water elemental, right?
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: A sea slug?
DM: A sea serpent.
Wellby: Oh. [laughs] Transforming into it on land and just like slo-
DM: Well, it's, it's-
Unknown: ... slopping around
DM: ... yeah, it has a move speed of 40.
DM: It has a swim speed of 120.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: But 40 isn't terrible.
Unknown: No, yeah.
Delwath: 14 to hit. Reach 21 target.
Seeker: How... Wait, how big is gargantuan?
Delwath: Gargantuan is-
DM: 20 foot by 20 foot
Unknown: ... yeah.
Seeker: Yeah. Yeah, I think that's-
DM: Oh. [laughs]
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Okay. If you turn into that.
Seeker: Yeah. I'm, I'm, I'm headed in that direction.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: That's, that
Delwath: is a pretty good... I don't see...
Delwath: I don't see m- I mean, a copper dragon also has a lot of
Delwath: things that might be good.
Seeker: Remember, I'll do this so long as nobody hits it.
DM: We can giant spin.
Seeker: Oh, perfect. [laughs] That is approximately the right size.
DM: Yeah, that's close enough for the right size.
Seeker: On the diagonal, it's a four by four.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: [coughs] Yeah. That's pretty much...
Delwath: Co- a copper dragon or a leviathan are your pretty much your...
Unknown: [items clattering] Yeah, that's perfect.
Unknown: [items clattering] [clears throat] Oh, yeah, of course.
Seeker: If you make something that we can pose this all on, that would be great.
Unknown: So everything-
Wellby: Yeah. I think I'm gonna do it with like a, like a meeting table in the middle, and then a little pool, and like a green wall of like trees and plants and stuff coming up.
Seeker: Oh, my God.
Delwath: Oh, you know what's pretty good?
Delwath: An ancient drass dragon.
Unknown: Hmm.
Delwath: CR 20.
Delwath: It makes... It has a sleep breath
Unknown: that
Delwath: each creature in a 90-foot cone, failure of the target has the incapacitated condition until the end of its next turn, at which point it repeats the save.
Delwath: Second failure, it's unconscious for 10 minutes.
Delwath: It wakes up if you do damage, but it has fire breath.
Delwath: So Schwartz, you like visualize the whole thing-
Wellby: Yep
Seeker: ... get like 30 parts to make it-
DM: Oh, thank you
Seeker: ... and then build it, and then do that again?
DM: Thank you.
Wellby: Yeah.
Seeker: I'm just watching you and thinking like, "How did you just
Seeker: come up with that?"
Wellby: Well, sure. Uh, no, thanks.
DM: All right.
Wellby: Yeah. It's visualizing, but it's not,
Wellby: it's not actually visualizing the end product.
Wellby: It's more like visualizing the concept of the end product.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Wellby: And then like building towards it, and in the building towards it, you're actually creating the thing.
Wellby: Like-
Unknown: Huh.
Wellby: It feels more like I'm visuali- like visualizing-
Seeker: You want just a sketch of like one
Wellby: ... yeah, or almost like a heuristic for how to go about-
Unknown: Oh
Wellby: ... moving through the process.
Seeker: Huh.
Wellby: Like I know I'm gonna use these kind of studs to build on, to attach greens and then-
Seeker: Oh, it's techniques that you're combining
Wellby: ... yeah. Yeah.
Wellby: Yeah.
Unknown: Ah.
Wellby: And then I'm gonna layer.
Wellby: So...
Unknown: But cool.
Wellby: Yeah. It's not actually visualizing the,
Wellby: like the final thing in all its detail.
Seeker: I was trying to... Like I, I have
Seeker: Technic stuff out.
Seeker: Izzy and I played with it a little bit. I'm like,
Seeker: it's, it helps you see like, wow, there's a lot of implicit knowledge [laughs] that goes into this.
Wellby: Yeah.
Seeker: Like you, she puts axles in things and then they fall out again.
Seeker: Oh, it needs to be secured on both ends.
Unknown: Like there's a-
Wellby: Yep
Seeker: ... way of thinking about-
Wellby: Right
Unknown: ... cutting parts.
Wellby: Yes. Yes.
DM: Did everybody level up to level 20?
Unknown: You can learn that.
Unknown: No.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: I guess they do
Wellby: ...
Unknown: Oh, thank you.
Wellby: Yeah. And like, do you have to learn that tactically?
Wellby: Like can you,
Wellby: can you only learn that by doing, maybe?
DM: Wow.
Unknown: I learned it.
DM: That's pretty strong. Your, your dex is now 25.
DM: You have a plus 7
DM: dexterity. Your wisdom is 22, and you have a plus 7.
Delwath: That makes your base AC is wisdom plus dex.
DM: Your AC is 24.
Wellby: Whoa.
Unknown: Oh my God.
Unknown: Wow.
Unknown: Unhittable.
DM: You d- you have plus 15 to hit with the staff and plus 13 with your fists.
Wellby: Holy shit.
Delwath: You know what's a pretty good-
DM: And your save DC for your aura strikes is now 20.
Wellby: Why did that jump up so much?
DM: 'Cause level 20 monk ability-
Delwath: He has plus four
DM: ... gives plus four to wisdom and plus four to dex.
Wellby: All right.
Seeker: Holy fuck.
Delwath: You know what's a good creature?
Seeker: I've set myself to 20.
Delwath: I might, I might ex- I might shapeshift.
Delwath: An animal lord.
Wellby: Animal lord?
Delwath: An animal lord. It's a celestial.
Delwath: It has four legendary resistances.
Kenzo: So imagine if it was like you build some shit, you try it, you take it apart.
Unknown: Um-
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: It makes two attacks plus-
Unknown: It's like hard work
Delwath: ... its attack isn't amazing.
Wellby: Which is not, like... Oh. It's not super efficient.
Unknown: 46.
Unknown: Um-
Wellby: Just gotta figure out what's going on. The process
Delwath: ... but it can summon an animal spirit.
Kenzo: You should give a guest lecture in, uh, Eric's, uh, learning, creative learning class.
Seeker: About Lego building?
Unknown: Yeah. [laughs] Or just how you...
Unknown: Yeah, I don't know.
Wellby: I feel like my lecture would be like, "Well, try some stuff.
Wellby: See how it goes."
Wellby: That's literally the whole point.
Wellby: Do something different. Like tell some more.
Unknown: That's like [laughs] literally the whole point.
Unknown: It is.
Kenzo: 'Cause like every conversation I have with Mitch is like, "This is really cool, but how can you tinker with it?"
Wellby: [laughs]
Seeker: Yeah. It's like, just like some more-
Kenzo: I mean, its attacks do less damage than like your attacks.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Yeah, but it has legendary resistance-
Unknown: It's okay
Delwath: ... to damage and saving throws
Unknown: ... you can do something else.
Wellby: [laughs] Don't, don't get too worried.
Delwath: So a lot more durable.
Unknown: Yep
Unknown: And
Unknown: it, um... [paper rustling]
DM: Okay.
Seeker: Leviathan. [beep] Let me get my Leviathan stat block on up here.
Seeker: But then it's like...
Seeker: This is somebody's GitHub page.
Seeker: Where am I looking? [paper rustling]
DM: Oh, you got one more spell too.
Unknown: Oh. [paper rustling]
DM: Uh, what's a good one?
Unknown: Can be any level?
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Although you're... You might want something that's not 9th level, because your 9th level slot's pretty tapped.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Honestly, Heroes' Feast is not a bad choice.
DM: That was always very useful to us.
Unknown: What's that do? Is it a bunch of like temporary hit points or what is that?
Delwath: No, actually, a good, a good buffing spell is a good idea.
DM: Okay. Or you could just take Force Cage.
DM: Although Force Cage is gonna do literally nothing but...
DM: 'cause the 100-foot long-
Unknown: Yes
DM: ... sized beast.
Seeker: I'll take Heroes' Feast.
Unknown: All right.
Delwath: But is there a better buff spell?
DM: No.
Unknown: What does Heroes' Feast give you?
DM: Uh, resistance to poison damage, immunity to frightened and poisoned conditions, increases your hit point maximum by 2d10.
Delwath: But it lasts for 24 hours, right?
DM: It lasts for 24 hours-
Unknown: That's what's good
DM: ... so it's key 'cause you can cast it before-
Delwath: Right
DM: ... the night before and then rest and get your slots back.
Delwath: All the other good buffs probably take your concentration, which you can't.
Unknown: [paper rustling]
Seeker: Okay, I think I added Heroes' Feast.
Seeker: What level is that one?
Unknown: Yeah. [paper rustling]
Seeker: Oh, and I can long rest even the...
Delwath: But what's the point of Heroes' Feast?
Delwath: Why wouldn't you just cast it with Wish?
Seeker: So I can save my Wish.
Delwath: No, but then you've rested.
DM: Oh, and then rest.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Yeah, that's true. Maybe Heroes' Feast isn't that useful.
Delwath: Because as a... The point of Heroes' Feast is it's 24 hours, so you can cast it the night before.
DM: Mm-hmm.
Delwath: But you can do it with Wish the night before.
Unknown: Oh.
Delwath: There's no upside to knowing it.
Delwath: [paper rustling] How m- Wait, how many 6th level slots do you have?
Unknown: Two.
Delwath: 'Cause it has to be any spell in the game, right?
Seeker: Yep. It's really helpful to have a magic consultant on your team.
Unknown: [laughs] Yes.
Kenzo: It's helpful to have a DM on your team too.
DM: [laughs] Well, yeah, exactly.
DM: [water running]
Unknown: Um..
Wellby: Magic consultant would be a great job title.
Unknown: That would be. [water running]
DM: [coughs]
Delwath: You want, you want...
Unknown: What does Seeker...
Delwath: Seeker needs a better... I think you need better ways of dealing damage.
Delwath: Although Chain Lightning's awful good.
DM: Well, Chain Lightning. That's why we added Chain Lightning.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: It's a really strong damage dealing spell.
Delwath: Is Chain Lightning 6th level?
DM: It's 6th level.
Delwath: I mean, there's an argument for something like,
Unknown: um...
Delwath: What I would, I would pick an 8th level.
DM: I- what about Demiplane? I mean, it's not gonna be useful in the next 30 hours, but it's this very Seeker-ish spell.
DM: [sniffs]
Unknown: What does that one do?
DM: It creates a demiplane that you can like-
Unknown: Oh, yeah
DM: ... stash stuff in.
Unknown: Yeah. Sh-
Seeker: sh- I'm into it. I feel like I've seen reference to that somewhere on my own character sheet.
Seeker: Is it like the wand or
Seeker: binding stones?
DM: Binding stones might have a demiplane-ish...
DM: 'Cause y- you only have one 8th level spell, and Animal Shapes is very, very useful but not every, not all the time.
Seeker: No, the binding stones don't have it.
Unknown: Hmm. All right.
Seeker: That was the Demiplane idea.
DM: I mean, the other potential useful 8th level spell is Mind Flay, which is also a 24-hour buff that gives you immunity to psychic damage and the
DM: charmed condition.
Wellby: Don't you have a ring that does that?
DM: Yeah, but...
Seeker: I don't know if I'm attuned to it right now.
Unknown: You're not.
DM: I don't think you're attuned to it 'cause...
Seeker: And also that's not exactly what the ring does.
DM: It just gives you, it gives you advantage against charm.
Delwath: I mean, actually demiplane's pretty useful 'cause we could, you...
Delwath: We could go to a demiplane. It lasts for an hour, so we can short rest in the demiplane and then come back out.
Unknown: Hmm.
DM: Yeah. I would probably just take demiplane.
Delwath: I, I would... Yeah, demiplane's actually a good ch- It, it, it is actually a really useful, "Hey, we need to...
Delwath: We need, we need 15...
Delwath: We need to go somewhere safe for a half hour to like..."
DM: Okay, so everybody's leveled up.
Unknown: All right.
Seeker: Go to demiplane.
DM: [sighs] Everybody long rest.
Unknown: Mm. Mm-hmm.
Kenzo: We don't get the ma- the temp edge HP things, right?
Kenzo: Why do we sometimes get that? Is that 'cause of something Delwath is doing?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Heroic Feast.
Delwath: Which temp HP thing?
Kenzo: Like a bunch... Sometimes you're like, "You have 28 HP, 28."
Delwath: Oh. Yeah, 'cause I cast Aid.
Unknown: Oh.
Delwath: But I generally cast Aid every morning.
Unknown: Nice.
Delwath: Because Aid as- lasts for eight hours.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: And I can
Delwath: cast it and then make breakfast and short rest again to get my spell slots back.
Unknown: Oh.
Delwath: So usually-
Unknown: You get 20.
Unknown: Yeah. [coughs]
DM: Okay, so let's, let's begin.
DM: As you wake up
DM: the morning after
DM: you left- Having returned from Limbo and immediately collapsed in exhaustion.
DM: As you awake,
DM: uh, the sun is rising over Orenlas on Vindasharna,
DM: and you are left now only with the mission to
DM: return to Isengai
DM: and find the ooze that once attempted to destroy your ship,
DM: destroy it, and cleanse the river so the Heartroot can be
DM: replanted.
DM: So [sighs] what, what is your...
DM: What do you want to do? I mean,
DM: you could just teleport straight there.
DM: You could fly the ship.
Seeker: How far are we up?
Delwath: Do we, do we know anything about the-
DM: You don't know anything that's happening in Isengai right now.
DM: You have many
DM: ways to figure that out.
Kenzo: [clears throat] Do some clairvoyance, send a-
Unknown: Scry.
Kenzo: Yeah. Scry. Let's do that.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: See what's going on.
Unknown: Oh, uh, Ken- Kenzo's-
Unknown: Yeah
Unknown: ... gonna, um,
Kenzo: uh, go hang out with the Heartroot and
Unknown: tell it-
DM: The Heartroot's still back in-
Delwath: We're in the Elven Forest.
DM: You're in the Elven Forest.
Delwath: Not the-
Kenzo: Oh, we have to go back and get the Heartroot.
Unknown: Or we can transport it.
DM: Yeah, or send a message to the rangers and say, "Bring the Heartroot."
Unknown: To have them bring it. Okay.
Delwath: But we should probably make the space.
Delwath: Like, let's not bring the Heartroot until we-
Unknown: Yeah
Delwath: ... need to then, right? Like-
DM: Don't want to risk it
Wellby: ... 'cause if this goes badly.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Could end badly, right?
Unknown: True that.
DM: Um.
Seeker: The transplantation we want to do as quickly as possible, you know?
Unknown: It's like, um,
Seeker: repotting a plant.
Unknown: Right.
Seeker: Replanting something. You want to keep it out of the ground.
DM: I mean, Seeker has two seventh level slots now.
DM: You probably want to teleport to Arbe's and then teleport to Isengai instantaneously with the Heartroot.
Unknown: Cool.
Seeker: Oh, I can take it in a teleport?
Seeker: It counts as a creature?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: I mean, it's 10 foot by 10... I mean, it's big, but, like, you could, you know,
DM: pick it up.
Unknown: Yeah. That'll be nice.
DM: Oh, but also you can teleport objects, can't you?
Unknown: I don't know.
Seeker: That seems like a real easy...
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: I think we-
DM: It, it's 600 miles from here, so it's about three days on, on...
DM: Two and a half days on Vindasharna.
Kenzo: We should bring the ship, yeah?
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: I think so, right? I think we just- There's no reason-
Unknown: We, we set out
Unknown: ... not.
Unknown: I mean, we'll, we'll-
Unknown: Gosh
Seeker: ... a single object.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: We'll set out-
Unknown: Use the levitation spell
Delwath: ... on Vindasharna towards Isengai.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Um...
Unknown: Scry.
DM: Yeah.
DM: Okay. So as the, you leave the monks here
DM: to
DM: either return and bring them back to Dunmar, to make their way to Dunmar, they all need a bit of time to recover before they're gonna be doing anything in the Elven Forest.
Unknown: Right.
DM: It's a good place to rest.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: And begin
DM: your trip.
DM: Uh, as you start to sail on Vindasharna, Delwath kicks out his silver bowl and begins to scry on,
DM: I guess, Isengai.
Delwath: The, yeah. Basically to start with where we were.
Delwath: I mean, basically the spot where Vindasharna was attacked last time.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Okay.
DM: So, um, you are looking down into a maelstrom of ash.
Unknown: Ah.
DM: You cannot see the city at all beneath you.
DM: It's like a, it's like a hurricane that seems to be growing and spreading out from the city, but now seems to be stretching about 15 miles in every direction
DM: from your scry.
Unknown: Of what?
DM: And the
DM: storm is growing bigger.
DM: [paper rustling]
Unknown: Ow. Hot.
Unknown: Huh.
Seeker: 15 miles in every direction.
Unknown: It's-
Wellby: And it's getting bigger?
DM: Yeah.
Wellby: All right, so maybe there's a little urgency.
Seeker: What... Is it drawing power from Limbo still or something else?
DM: You can't see. All that Delwath can see in the scrying mirror is-
Delwath: [laughs] You know, you know everything I know, Seeker.
Kenzo: Ah, yeah.
DM: [clears throat] A maelstrom of ash swirling below him.
Unknown: Hmm.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: okay. And it's, like, 600 miles away?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Um,
Seeker: hmm. There was the question of the effect of the
Wellby: explosion we saw inside Limbo-
DM: Yeah
Unknown: ... onto this world.
Unknown: Um...
Unknown: Maybe it's a backlash.
Unknown: [clears throat]
Unknown: Let's see. Um,
Delwath: I, I think the faster
Kenzo: we can get there, the better.
Delwath: Um, but I think-
Seeker: Well, we don't want to teleport into a hurricane.
Delwath: No, I think we probably don't want to teleport into a hurricane.
Unknown: I think that's true.
Unknown: Um.
Seeker: But what kind of approach even is there to fight something so big?
Unknown: I...
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: Um, arcana about
Seeker: giant oozes? Is there anything, any precedent for...
Kenzo: Wait, the oozes is from Limbo, right?
Kenzo: It's a Limbo ooze. We really don't know, right?
Delwath: We don't know at all
Delwath: anything about the ooze.
Wellby: ... Arcana about oozes whatsoever
Delwath: Literally all we know about the ooze-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... is we saw it from above, right?
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Delwath: When we flew over Isengai before, we saw this giant ooze like thing-
Unknown: And we-
Delwath: ... covering like half the city.
Delwath: And we flew down towards it to investigate, and then it flung a tendril off like-
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Remember, yeah, yeah.
Seeker: Like we know like what color it was and w- that the fact that it-
Unknown: Yeah, but
Seeker: ... was able to use acid to damage the stone of the ship.
Kenzo: Yeah. No, but, but my qu- It's just...
Kenzo: 'Cause Rai and the monks went to Isengai 'cause that's where the...
Unknown: Right?
DM: That's where the Limbo... Yes, that was where the Limbo-
Unknown: Where the ooze was
Unknown: ... woo was.
Delwath: Wait, but they didn't go to Isengai.
Delwath: Did they go to Isengai?
Unknown: They went, yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Oh, okay. They went to Isengai.
Kenzo: Yeah. So the, the... So I'm saying the ooze is related to Limbo, right?
Kenzo: It's not like the ooze is-
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
DM: The ooze was not there when Rai and the monks went there.
Unknown: And then-
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: Oh, it wasn't there when Rai and the monks went there?
Unknown: No.
Unknown: Oh, okay.
Kenzo: That's the whole thing. It was like a consequence of them like trying to close the vortex or some shit like that.
Kenzo: Either the ooze leaked out-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... or it's like, it's like some Limbo ooze or something.
Seeker: So maybe we can use Limbo tricks on it.
Seeker: [thud] Like transmute it with our minds.
Unknown: Maybe.
Seeker: From inside Limbo.
Wellby: I don't know if we wanna go back to Limbo, though.
Unknown: I don't-
Delwath: No, Limbo's... Let's stay out of Limbo for right now.
Unknown: [dice rolling]
Seeker: But then can we banish it, then?
Kenzo: Ah, that's an interesting question.
Kenzo: That's an interesting question.
Unknown: Feel like that'd be... Feel like that might be a little too easy. [laughs]
Seeker: Is it a creature?
DM: It is definitely a creature, yes.
Wellby: Is it n... How do we find out if it's native to a different-
Kenzo: Uh, did I s- I mean, I must have soul sighted it or like kind of-
Unknown: Ah. Oh
Unknown: ... so contacted other planes.
Unknown: The finding stones.
Delwath: I'm gonna ask the Tantri.
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: Is the ooze a
Delwath: native to Limbo?
Delwath: A creature of Limbo?
Unknown: Sort of. [clears throat]
Kenzo: This is like us fighting the sentient ocean, basically.
Delwath: Hold on. I have five questions.
Seeker: Oh, keep going. Yeah.
Delwath: It's sort of native to Limbo.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: uh, it, um...
Unknown: Is it,
Unknown: is it [coughs]...
Delwath: Um, does it have gold?
Unknown: Oh, interesting. [laughs]
Unknown: No.
Unknown: Um.
Unknown: Great question.
Unknown: Does it, uh,
Unknown: um...
Delwath: Does it have...
Unknown: [coughs]
Seeker: I've got an idea here.
Unknown: Um.
Unknown: Duh, does it...
Unknown: [thud] Um,
Delwath: I'm trying to think of how to ask this. Can, can...
Delwath: This isn't qui- not quite the right phrasing.
Delwath: Can it be killed by stabbing?
Delwath: But I don't mean exactly that. Like
Delwath: can we, can we destroy it with the tools and capabilities, uh, we would use against sort of a normal creature?
Seeker: A normal magical creature?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Sort of. [laughs]
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: is it growing?
Unknown: Hmm.
Unknown: Yes.
Delwath: Um, one more.
Unknown: Uh,
Unknown: does it have allies?
Unknown: Ooh.
Unknown: That's a good one.
Seeker: Good question.
Unknown: No.
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: So it's growing, so I think
Delwath: maybe a leisurely flight to the ooze could backfire.
Kenzo: No. Well, I mean, we should get close, but not...
Delwath: I'm wondering if we could just teleport, but we can't really tele-
Unknown: Can we, do we have... We don't really have the capability.
DM: Remember you also took wind walk,
Unknown: Eric.
Seeker: That can make us gaseous.
DM: And you can, you gain a fly speed of 300-
Unknown: Oh. Oh, wow. That's fast
DM: ... feet. So.
Delwath: How long does that last?
DM: Eight hours.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: 300 feet
DM: per six seconds.
Unknown: That seems useful.
DM: Is 35 miles per hour.
DM: No, sorry, it's 600 feet per six seconds 'cause you can dash.
DM: 68 miles per hour.
Unknown: And-
Delwath: Way faster than the ship And we have 600 miles to go.
DM: Well, no, 'cause you've been flying for
DM: a couple of hours, so you have-
Delwath: Well, we can go 544 miles.
Delwath: So do we have about 500 miles and 50 miles to go?
DM: You have like 580 miles to go.
Delwath: So wind walk would get us almost all the way there
Delwath: in a day.
Seeker: But do we wanna still have it up when we're encountering the thing?
DM: No, because the only actions you can take in wind form are-
Unknown: Ah
Delwath: ... dash or revert to your normal form.
Wellby: Why would we not just teleport if we wanna get there quick?
Delwath: We... What would we teleport to?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: I just-
Seeker: 'Cause we wanna be like not in the side of it, but at the edge of it.
Seeker: We wanna approach it, I think.
Wellby: We've s... Yeah, we, uh-
Seeker: We have seen it
Wellby: ... can we tele- We don't have to teleport...
Wellby: Do we have to teleport to the ground? Can we teleport to the location above Isengai where we last passed over it?
Seeker: That seems too dangerous.
Kenzo: When we got attacked by the tendril.
Unknown: Yeah, well, yeah.
Unknown: I've s-
Delwath: Wait, Seeker just said teleport seems too dangerous?
Seeker: No, being right above it.
Unknown: Are, are you okay, Seeker? [laughs]
Seeker: It's not about the accuracy, which I can guarantee.
Seeker: [laughs] It's about the acid tendrils.
Delwath: But we could be wind walking.
Delwath: We could wind walk.
Seeker: Which really affect my ability to do my job.
Delwath: And then teleport as wind form and then scatter.
DM: No, because the only actions you can take
DM: ... dash or move up
Unknown: Right.
Kenzo: Well, I, it feels like we still need to do some reconnaissance, right?
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: So why don't we, why don't we get Vinresharna, like, close-ish?
Unknown: It'll take a long time.
Unknown: Yeah. We'll do it... Well, we'll do both.
Seeker: It's quick. We'll go a little ways further on Vinresharna.
DM: Because the ooze is growing.
Unknown: Huh?
DM: The ooze is growing.
Unknown: How fast?
Delwath: I didn't think to ask that, but also that's not a yes or no question.
Seeker: Let's get close enough to Vinresharna that Wind Walk gets us within-
Unknown: That's what I'm saying
Seeker: ... a few miles.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: That you're... Right now.
Seeker: Oh. Oh, let's do it right now then, yeah.
Delwath: If we Wind Walk now, in eight hours we'd be, like, 10 miles from it.
DM: You'd be 10 miles away.
Seeker: Yeah, let's just do that.
DM: Or 15 miles away.
Seeker: This is the fastest way for us to get there and-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... to be able to teleport right on top of it.
Seeker: Yeah. Great.
Unknown: Perfect.
Unknown: Got it. Done.
DM: So let's-
DM: So you set Falljer to keep-
Unknown: Fast traveling
DM: ... following along behind, as he's gotten used to you by now.
DM: Seeker casts Wind Walk, and you fly-
Delwath: Is that 7th level or 8th level?
DM: 6th.
Unknown: 6th level.
Delwath: Oh, good. So you can still cast Demiplane if we gotta hide.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: Oh, there you go.
Seeker: I was looking at the binding stones spells
Seeker: because I think it's... There's a chance we could guess the proper combination of three stones to bind this creature.
Unknown: Ooh.
Delwath: I mean, I like Seeker's chances here.
Unknown: You sh-
Delwath: There's a cha-... I mean-
Seeker: The, the question is-
Delwath: You mean 100% chance, right, Seeker?
Unknown: [laughs]
Seeker: We're talking about my intelligence here.
Delwath: Right. Yeah, so [laughs] I have full faith in Seeker's ch- magical chances.
Unknown: But
Seeker: the question is what
Seeker: spell attack this looks like.
Unknown: Um.
Seeker: The following spells are rumored to be part of the abilities of the stones.
Delwath: Imprisonment, is that one of them?
Seeker: Snare, Web, Watery Sphere, Magic Circle, Planar Binding, and Imprisonment, which I was just looking at.
Delwath: Imprisonment's pretty good.
Seeker: But it's not permanent. Or is it?
Unknown: Wait.
Delwath: I thought Imprisonment was semi-permanent.
Wellby: Well, could we show the ooze the mirror?
Wellby: It probably doesn't have a soul that can [laughs] be trapped that way.
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: That'd be pretty amazing though.
Seeker: Oh my God. That's a funny idea.
Unknown: Where are its eyes though, you know?
DM: The downside to Imprisonment is there's a save.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
Seeker: And this thing, like, probably has legendary resistance in its-
Unknown: Yes.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: So you can... The, the mirror would never work on anything with a legendary resistance.
Delwath: I mean, Imprisonment lasts until it's dispelled.
Unknown: Right.
Delwath: But honestly, it feels a little bit like...
Delwath: That's kinda like-
Seeker: Shortcutting the whole thing
Delwath: ... it's shoving the problem down to somebody else, right?
Delwath: Like, you know [laughs] when somebody comes along and dispels Imprisonment, the ooze'll just come back.
Kenzo: Well, this is like what I was saying before.
Kenzo: If we did, like, a, a before, uh, before Talgar our time thing.
Kenzo: Like, we just, we end the campaign by imprisoning some crazy-
Delwath: We imprisoned the ooze [laughs] at the end of the last campaign
Unknown: ... thing.
Unknown: Oh, gotcha.
Seeker: Exactly. Exactly. No, you don't sit down, you know?
Seeker: We then use Minimus Containment.
Seeker: The target becomes one inch tall and is trapped inside an indestructible gemstone or similar object.
Delwath: Yeah, but we did that in the previous campaign and it was a little gemstone in Limbo that was...
Delwath: It was trapped, and then when Rai tried to pull Limbo, the gemstone broke, the spell was dispelled, and then the ooze came out.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: That's how the next campaign ends.
Delwath: The next campaign ends [laughs] with us imprisoning the ooze.
Wellby: Just an endless series of pushing the problem into the future.
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: [laughs] 'Cause it can be dispelled is the point.
Delwath: Imprisonment's not permanent, it's just until it's dispelled.
Seeker: Well, we'll just carry it with us in the, in the portal hole.
Wellby: [laughs] Too big for the hole.
Unknown: No, it's one inch tall.
DM: No, no.
Wellby: Oh, oh. That's right, yeah.
DM: The Minimus Containment is, makes it-
Delwath: It's like, you know, it's like the little classic-
DM: You trap it in a hole
Delwath: ... little de- demon trapped in a gemstone.
Wellby: Would be crazy not to.
Delwath: The real problem is it's guaranteed to fail because the ooze is guaranteed to have at least one legendary resistance.
DM: You'd have to burn all of them.
Delwath: We'd have to m- we'd have to burn all our switches.
Seeker: Yeah. We, we need a variety of tactics here in our pocket.
Unknown: Now-
Seeker: So this is one option
Delwath: ... the an- wait, the answer was can we kill it was sort of?
DM: Can you,
DM: can you kill it?
DM: It was y- yeah.
DM: Well, it was mostly.
Unknown: Right. Okay.
Delwath: So I mean, it is an idea to, to be like, wow, if we, if we wear it down and it's, it's, like, vulnerable to a spell, then
Delwath: that's a possibility.
Seeker: I'd say I'll keep the binding stones in my pocket 'cause they're always in my pocket.
Delwath: Right. [laughs] I mean, nothing could possibly go wrong using them for the very first time in a high stakes combat situation, right?
Seeker: That's what they've been there for, waiting their turn the whole time.
Unknown: You need to use the binding-
Unknown: That's right
Wellby: ... how did you not use the binding stones yet?
Unknown: That's right.
Kenzo: You gotta use those.
Seeker: It's... I've looked at them as an option many times.
Seeker: It's like, huh.
Delwath: Th- it's not super clear how they work.
Delwath: Like, do you have specific th- you don't actually know what they can do, right?
Seeker: None of the abilities are combat things 'cause, like-
Unknown: Right
Seeker: ... Imprisonment is one minute, so.
Unknown: Right. Right.
Seeker: That's really the issue.
Unknown: Right.
Delwath: Okay. So we are...
DM: So you now, you fly as
DM: gaseous clouds,
DM: 70 miles an hour racing across the landscape of, landscape of the Plaguelands following the river from...
DM: That just goes down from the Orenlas Forest to join the Istaros right near Isengai.
DM: Um, you pass over a
DM: huge extance- expanse of,
DM: uh, completely burned forest-
Unknown: [coughs]
DM: ... with trees still standing.
DM: It's, like, blackened and burned.
Seeker: That's weird.
DM: Um, you pass over a open,
DM: um,
DM: uh-
Delwath: Wait, that's just south of Orenlas?
DM: That's, um, halfway between Orenlas and
DM: Isengai, roughly.
Delwath: Do you know what's th- just out of game-
DM: Yeah
Delwath: ... do you know what's there? Okay. Wait, I might talk to you about that separately.
DM: Okay. Um- You pass over
DM: a,
DM: um, large expanse
DM: of [coughing] rolling hills, um, and piles of ash and slag that swirl and blow in the wind.
Wellby: You don't think we did this, right?
Wellby: You know, this is not related to what happened in Limbo.
Seeker: Almost certainly there are side effects here of the-
Unknown: No, this predates what happened in Limbo
Wellby: Okay. Okay
Unknown: This is the Plaguelands.
Wellby: Oh.
Delwath: I mean, we did it by not stopping Sha'mutte from-
Wellby: Okay, okay
Delwath: ... creating the great plague, but-
Wellby: But this is not related to the, like-
Unknown: No
Wellby: ... ash explosion.
DM: No.
Unknown: Um-
Wellby: Okay. Okay.
DM: And then you-
Wellby: Feel better
DM: ... um, cross
DM: a slow meandering ash clogged river
DM: and follow it until you can see the edge of this...
DM: In fact, where Wis- where Windwalk ends is basically at the edge of this growing ash storm, which is about 15 miles away from the, from Isengai.
Seeker: Oh my God.
DM: And you're standing on a hill,
DM: a low hill. Actually, as you settle out of wind form your feet sink about six inches into ash,
DM: and
DM: you're walking across. It's like a lunar landscape.
DM: Everything is just coated in
DM: dust and ash. You're looking-
Unknown: This might be because of what we did in
Unknown: Limbo.
DM: You're looking across-
Unknown: Ash is a triggering word.
Unknown: Yeah [laughs].
DM: You're looking across this growing storm that looks like
DM: a, almost like a hurricane with winds blowing up to make...
DM: that's picking up the ash on the ground and making a, an
DM: obscured wall
DM: beyond which you can't see.
Seeker: We don't even know if there's news here at all.
Unknown: I mean-
Wellby: Huh
Unknown: ... that's true.
Seeker: We shouldn't make too many assumptions.
Seeker: Well, how do we find out what's going on here?
Seeker: I could clairvoyance inside it-
Unknown: Um-
Seeker: ... but I'll just see ash.
Delwath: Yep. How far away is it?
DM: Isengai is about 15 miles from here.
DM: You're at the edge of the ash storm, and it's creeping towards you.
Kenzo: Wellby, should you send some animals into this?
Wellby: Uh, I mean, I-
Unknown: They'll die
Wellby: ... we already know what the result will be [laughs].
Delwath: I mean, I have an i- uh, hold on.
Unknown: Um-
Kenzo: How can we recon without-
Delwath: I have an idea. Can we get a little closer?
Delwath: Let's go a little closer.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: I mean, you can walk.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
DM: Just keep walking. But you're gonna walk into the storm if you go more than about two miles.
Delwath: Okay. Let's go to the edge of the storm,
Delwath: right? So like let's- I wanna stop like 500 feet from the edge of the storm.
DM: Well, it's not, it's... as you get closer, it's not, it's not like a sharp edge.
Unknown: Okay
DM: It's like there's winds blowing, and you can see maybe 200 yards into the storm as you get closer.
DM: Just from a distance it looks
DM: like, it looks like the edge of a thunderstorm or something, right?
DM: So there's like, you can see an edge, but there's winds blowing and it's picking up the ash.
DM: Um, the winds just get more intense as you go in, and so the ash on the ground is being lifted and tossed.
Delwath: Um, hold on one second.
Delwath: Uh, there's 10 rounds in a minute.
Delwath: Wow, this is actually, this can go a long way.
Delwath: Wait, is that right?
Delwath: So if something can move,
Delwath: if something can move 120 feet and it can m- take two moves in a turn, right?
Delwath: That, if it's running, something that, that can move 120, it could go 240 feet every six seconds, right?
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Okay. So 240 feet every six seconds is like half a mile every minute,
Delwath: right? So in an hour-
DM: Well, you can't, unless you're in wind form, you can't dash every round for an hour
Delwath: What if you're an intangible creature?
DM: Possibly then you could, I guess.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: oh, no. It can only move...
Delwath: Yeah, you can up to twice...
Delwath: Oh, no, no, no, no. It can't.
Delwath: Never mind, I c- it's only half that speed.
Delwath: That's okay. It only needs to be half that speed.
Delwath: Um, 14 miles.
Unknown: So
Delwath: 14 miles, I mean, the Heart of Isengai is...
Delwath: The, the distance from here to the ooze is probably only
Delwath: 10 miles, right? We think.
DM: Somewhere between 10 and 15 miles.
Delwath: Okay. So when we get close, Delwath will disappear, and an identical copy of Delwath appears right next to Delwath.
Unknown: What?
Delwath: And Delwath says, "It's okay.
Delwath: Don't, I'm still here, invisible,"
Delwath: and sends his copy running into the...
Delwath: This is mislead.
Wellby: Delwath two.
Delwath: Yeah, Delwath two. The first new...
Unknown: Yes.
Unknown: So-
Unknown: What?
Unknown: This-
Seeker: Well, strictly speaking, three, 'cause there was a semi-chron Delwath.
Unknown: That's true. Um-
Wellby: Oh, yeah
Delwath: ... so it's an illusory double, right?
Delwath: The double lasts for the duration.
Delwath: You can move the double up to twice your speed.
Delwath: You can see through its eyes and hear through his ear, ears as if you were located where it was.
Unknown: That's awesome.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Perfect.
Unknown: So-
Unknown: Wow
Unknown: ...
Unknown: it can-
Seeker: It can run into the ash. Yeah
Delwath: ... it just runs right into the ash. It's, it's a,
Delwath: it's intangible and invulnerable.
Wellby: That's perfect.
Kenzo: That's amazing. So perfect.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
Wellby: That's exactly what we need.
Delwath: So like since my speed is, is 60, it can move 120 each turn.
Delwath: Then I can take attack, magic action.
Delwath: So-
Unknown: One Delwath prime
Unknown: ... um-
DM: Very good
Delwath: ... so it's 120 feet, so every minute it moves 200, it moves 100 and, 1,200 feet.
DM: It's, it's 120 feet per round, right?
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: So it can move 14 miles in an hour.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: And the spell lasts for an hour, which is why the hour matters.
Delwath: But I'm just gonna
Delwath: send it, but it uses my senses, so it has true sight, it has dark vision.
Delwath: I mean, I can see through it with my senses as if I, I'm at- As if you were ...
Delwath: as if I made an observation.
Unknown: What do you see?
DM: Uh, oh, wait, hold on.
Unknown: Mm.
Kenzo: Didn't think we'd just run right through the ash, did you, Tim?
DM: Uh, no, I'm just calculating, um,
DM: when it's gonna get to where,
DM: where you see. So you run,
DM: um,
DM: through
DM: a growing storm of wind.
DM: Um, the first couple of miles, uh, it's maybe lightly obscured as you're crossing across these sort of rolling hills that were once pleasant agricultural
DM: valleys. Um, there is no structures remaining here whatsoever.
DM: Any villages or towns or anything have long since been destroyed.
DM: Over the course of the next six miles or so, so eight miles total, you...
DM: ash gets denser and denser until, um, about, I don't know, two thirds of the way into the spell, it's, the visibility is something like only about
DM: 30 feet in front of you.
DM: You can see hardly anything.
DM: Um,
DM: True Sight is irrelevant here 'cause you're, it's ash.
Unknown: Yeah. Yep.
DM: You keep running.
DM: Uh, slightly further, you, uh, after about 50 minutes, um, or no, it's a little bit before that, um, 45 minutes, you start to
DM: pass through the...
DM: uh, I mean, no, maybe about 50 minutes, the outskirts of what might have been Isinge.
DM: You can see just every now and then, like mostly it's completely destroyed, but every now and then you'll see a,
DM: you know, a part of a wall standing or like a little stretch of, um, buildings that kind of make a little bit of a, of a bit of a road,
DM: pillars standing like that.
DM: Um,
DM: at,
DM: uh, 59 minutes and, uh...
Seeker: Oh, it lasts an hour?
DM: It lasts an hour.
Delwath: Oh, you know what? Hold on.
Delwath: It lasts two hours.
Delwath: I'm gonna metamagic it.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: It's why, why it's better to double the duration.
DM: All right.
Unknown: That's more useful.
DM: Okay. Well, at 59 minutes and 24 seconds, um,
DM: it comes to a,
DM: like the eye of a hurricane style, like very intense wind.
Unknown: Oh, wait, hold on. I might not be able to do...
Unknown: hold on. I can't rem- hold on.
Kenzo: Keep talking. A, an eye, okay.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: And you stumble through into a clear open space.
Unknown: Ooh.
DM: Um, about 600 feet across, um, still lightly obscured as mist and ash sort of drift in through the center
DM: of the storm. Um,
DM: there is, uh,
DM: there's a, there's a dome overhead, so it's like there's a, the clouds, the ash clouds are sort of sitting on top, so you can't see the sky from here.
Delwath: Oh, yeah, I can only double range, not, or duration, so it's...
DM: Well, you have, uh-
Unknown: 30 seconds
DM: ... 36 seconds
DM: of it inside the clear spot.
DM: Um, three things that you quickly notice from inside the clear spot.
DM: Uh,
DM: first, um,
DM: you can see... this is, this is, at the very edge of the clear spot, um, maybe just be- like just beyond the wall, like you can see it sloping down towards the river.
DM: You can't actually see the river.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: It's on the other side of the, of the ash.
DM: Um, but you can see the docks, like where the, the river port would have started.
DM: There's a, a few little buildings that suggest.
DM: Um, there is a, um, in the center here, there's what might have used to have been a plaza or something, or a city well or something like that,
DM: and you can see like a, a big well like this that's cracked and split.
DM: And stretching out from the well, you see a, one like long pseudopod of some kind of ooze-like creature.
Delwath: So it's stretching from the well into the ash?
DM: No, no, into the clear spot.
DM: It's like-
Seeker: Mostly it's in the well
DM: ... mostly it's in the well.
Unknown: Ah.
DM: And there's like one pseudopod that's-
Unknown: It's coming out of the well
Delwath: ... coming out of the well, and it's just like-
Unknown: Yeah ... okay. Feeling around
DM: ... feeling around.
Seeker: I wonder if it went there to hide from the ash storm.
Unknown: Maybe.
Seeker: Yeah. Does this, does it look like it's hiding?
Kenzo: Does, does it look like it doesn't like the ash?
Delwath: Does it react to somebody walking up to it?
DM: Um-
Delwath: I mean, it looks like Delweth. You don't know it's an illusion unless it-
DM: Uh, yeah, like three more pseudopods shoot out of the well and start...
DM: something-
Unknown: I mean, Del-
DM: ... starts pulling and crawling, and you start to see like this bubbly mass start to ooze up out of the well.
Delwath: The illusion of Delweth.
DM: It starts to rush towards you.
Delwath: Draw a sword and charge it.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: What does it do?
DM: Uh, it's, um...
DM: uh, what do you see?
Unknown: Hmm?
DM: It is going to-
Unknown: What do you see?
DM: ... three, three pseudopods come flying,
DM: all three straight towards Delweth.
DM: Once, when you hit about 60 feet away from it,
DM: like three of these acidic pods, pseudopods just like shoot out across the plaza to strike at you.
DM: But nothing happens because you're too vulnerable and usually, and now you have about six seconds left.
Seeker: So wait, what about Kong's question?
Unknown: Is it-
DM: Sorry, what was your question?
Seeker: Is it harmed by the ash?
Unknown: The ooze.
DM: It doesn't,
DM: it doesn't seem to care about the ash particularly.
Unknown: Oh.
Seeker: Like it doesn't stay inside the eye?
DM: Well, the, the area's like 600 feet across.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: It's in the middle. What it looks like is that it, like lives in the sewers.
Unknown: Ah.
DM: And it is now crawl...
DM: It's like was looking at– poked out of this well and is looking around.
DM: Maybe it's simultaneously looking out of every well in the city.
Unknown: [coughs]
Kenzo: Oh no, collective consciousness ooze.
Unknown: [clears throat] Well,
Delwath: double Delweth will charge and disappear.
Unknown: Okay.
Delwath: And then I'll cast Scrying at that spot.
Unknown: Nice.
Unknown: Oh, very good.
Delwath: 'Cause now I've seen it.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: So now we can, in, we have, in a more leisurely fashion, take 10 minutes to look around and see what we see.
DM: So the... You see now spreading out-
Delwath: And then we can teleport there
DM: ... about 100-
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: That's exactly what I was gonna do.
Unknown: 100 feet.
Unknown: Well done.
DM: Stretching about 100 feet wide, you can see now this like bubbling mass that seems to be searching around the edges of the plaza with these pseudopods, like trying
DM: to figure out what happened to this creature that vanished.
Unknown: Is it like-
Seeker: Not very smart
Delwath: ... filling up the whole-
DM: No. It's like 100 f- the, the center of the mass is like maybe only 80 or 100 feet across, but it ha- but these pseudopods extend.
Delwath: Are there any like buildings or places to hide in this clearing?
DM: Um, there's,
DM: uh, all that sur- like most of this has been...
DM: It seems actually possibly, um, s- partially consumed by the ooze, because as it's bubbling out, you see like little bits of stone and stuff like floating and decaying in this body.
DM: But there is what might have once been a,
DM: a, like a, a covered market or something.
DM: There's a row of columns that are each about 10 feet tall, and then the roof has cracked and fallen down, and there's like a line, a diagonal line that goes about 40 feet long
DM: of piled rubble.
Delwath: And did you say before this, the river runs right past this, like the bank of the river?
DM: The river is like, so I'll just...
DM: It's not a, this is not... That's a bad sketch, but the basic.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So the well, there's like a big plaza like this.
DM: Somewhere like here is the river, but you can't see it 'cause the ash goes like that, but you can see like docks and infrastructure that suggests the river is that way.
Delwath: Okay, so this was probably a riverside plaza.
DM: Yeah, and then there's a, what once was a market here where all that remains is the front row of columns.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: But there's a roof that fell and, um, fo- forms a line of rubble.
Delwath: I'm just trying to think about why this would be-
Unknown: It's a-
Delwath: ... an eye of a storm.
Seeker: I was wondering the same thing. Why is it here?
Kenzo: Okay, so one, one thing.
Kenzo: Do we have ways... 'Cause like it feels like we're-
Unknown: Water check
Kenzo: ... it feels like we're gonna have to end up in the sewer.
Kenzo: Like, like whatever the ooze, the ooze is like down.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: It's down there someplace, so.
Delwath: Or we draw it out. Yeah.
Kenzo: Or we draw it out, but I'll, like again, it, it feels like however we're gonna defeat this thing, it's not gonna be like, like chopping off some pseudopod tendrils.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: You know? There's like a-
Wellby: There must be like some core or center or brain or something.
Kenzo: Exactly. Exactly. Exactly. There's, there's gotta be s- and, and that's likely deep underground.
Unknown: The ooze nugget.
Unknown: What's that?
Seeker: The ooze nugget.
Kenzo: Yeah, whatever. The ooze, yeah, the ooze, the ooze central nervous system brain thing.
Unknown: It's the super brain thing.
Kenzo: Is there a way for us to like explore in the sewers, like without going there?
Kenzo: Like can we like, uh, you know, drone map it or something?
Kenzo: Like how do we, uh...
Seeker: Oh, 'cause your thing that you can send out can't go very far, but we can send a bat to die.
Unknown: The thing I can send out can go super far.
Unknown: It's just-
Seeker: Like the one you just did.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: Can you do that again?
Delwath: Yeah, but we'd have to be...
Delwath: The problem is we're 15 miles from-
Seeker: Oh, we're at the r- we're at range.
Delwath: We're 15 miles from here.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: So I can create an illusory double of myself that lasts for an hour.
Unknown: Huh.
Delwath: But, and it can move twice my speed,
Delwath: but otherwise it's the same as Delweth, so like it doesn't have...
Kenzo: It can't like cast spells and fight and stuff.
Delwath: No.
Kenzo: Yeah. No, but for, for, this is perfect.
Unknown: For, for the reconnaissance it's perfect.
Kenzo: We, so we wanna go... Yeah. Like, right?
Delwath: Like is there a good way to map the sewer?
Unknown: I mean-
Kenzo: Or go check out the sewer without going in there
Seeker: ... can we animal shapes you, you fly out above the eye of the storm, briefly turn into Delweth while falling, cast your double,
Delwath: and then you can-
Unknown: And then die [laughs]
Seeker: ... re animal shape and then fly back.
Delwath: No, you have to re animal shape me.
Seeker: I can't from a distance.
Unknown: Exactly.
Seeker: Can you switch? I think you can go back and forth now.
Delwath: Can you switch yourself with animal shape?
Seeker: I think so.
Unknown: Okay.
Kenzo: Tim, is the sewer, is the ooze just like clogging up the sewer entirely, or is it, or the, the well-
Delwath: Why don't you, why don't you...
Kenzo: Oh, yeah. Yeah, uh, Tim, fucking, uh, commune with nature.
Unknown: What the hell's going on?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Ah.
Unknown: Oh my God. Oh my God.
DM: So many things are going on.
DM: Yeah. Can you... It's just, oh my God. What the fuck?
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: Commune with nature and then also, yeah, dude, like, like the ooze like, like 'cause it's, it's an e- it's an entity, right?
Kenzo: It's got a consciousness. Like-
Delwath: Can you get like a radar map?
Kenzo: That's what I'm saying. Yeah. Well, also to...
Kenzo: And, and if it is, like it, this is actually really interesting.
Kenzo: Is the consciousness like uniformly, um, exhibited throughout the physical system of the ooze?
Unknown: Mm. Mm-hmm.
Kenzo: Or is it centralized into like a, you know, like the core, the brain of the consciousness is like, you know, deep down.
Kenzo: Anyways, what's going on?
DM: Ah, okay.
Unknown: Commune with nature first.
DM: Uh, yes.
DM: Um, actually for this one I'm gonna say make a insight check.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Um, it has to be Seeker that turns, that turns back in.
DM: It's the spell cast that brings her back.
Seeker: That's what I thought. I was just looking it up and found that out too.
Kenzo: What's my, is my insight like plus a billion now?
DM: Your insight is gonna be like, it's gonna be plus high now, 'cause you got better wisdom.
DM: Plus 12 or 13 or something like that.
Kenzo: Yeah. Plus 12, that's nice.
Unknown: It's so... Oh, yeah.
Kenzo: Wow. Oh my God. Oh, this is so cool.
Kenzo: All my things are so much more awesome now.
Unknown: This is great. All right.
Unknown: Plus 12.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Great.
DM: So Kenza goes into his trance and reaches out your consciousness for you can now stretch something like 40 miles or something like that.
Unknown: Wow.
Kenzo: I think you started at nine and four, so let's go one then
DM: Oh, yeah
Delwath: But whatever.
DM: Yeah, yeah, whatever. It doesn't matter.
DM: It's plenty long enough to, to get a sense of this place.
DM: Um,
DM: there are...
DM: The first, the first thing you notice is that there is,
DM: um,
DM: there is not a single, there's not like one...
DM: You don't sense any like single consciousness.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: In fact, it's hard to describe this as a consciousness at all.
DM: What you sense is a,
DM: um,
DM: like just a disordering of...
DM: It's actually like, it reminds you of the Heartroot, but completely inverted by chaos.
Unknown: Ooh, Chaosroot.
DM: And it's stre- like, you can see actually the n- you actually suspect that what you're seeing in your mind as you stretch through is like a map of the sewers.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: And tunnels underneath the city where you see like lines of this.
DM: It's almost like the filamentous, like-
Kenzo: Yeah, mycelial
DM: ... mycelial of the Heartroot.
Unknown: Yeah
DM: But all like Limbo Ooze network instead.
Delwath: So it's the anti-Heartroot.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: But it is concentrated most strongly in,
DM: uh, it is densest, the like structure is densest in three places.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: Three places.
DM: Um,
DM: one is in the river.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: The second is, um,
DM: what you guess is this pl- like it, what it feels like is...
DM: So you're doing this while Delwath is scrying, and you're sort of layering on your like radar consciousness map of what Delwath is seeing, and it feels like it's dr- like
DM: it's condensing.
DM: So around the s- the center of this plaza, the consciousness is very thin, and it's all like pulled together into a...
DM: It's almost like it extract, it pulled bits of itself from all the sewers around here to emerge out and search for Delwath.
DM: Right. So it's like the density is higher here.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
DM: It's condensed here.
DM: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: [coughs]
Unknown: That's interesting.
Seeker: There's, wait, there's a third.
DM: The third is at this, there is something else at this location that doesn't feel like a consciousness.
DM: It feels like,
DM: um,
DM: so-
Wellby: Hang on. Something else, like not the Ooze whatsoever at all?
DM: Maybe it's related to the Ooze.
DM: It's hard to say.
DM: It's...
DM: So when you were, when you were attempting, when you were like vibing with the tree in-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... Limbo, right, and you got your little chaos key,
DM: uh,
DM: there's a, there's like a flavor of the plane that you sense, and there's like a scar, like a nodule or some kind of,
DM: um,
DM: something like that that has the same taste in your mind.
DM: Some like little bit of Limbo at the bottom of this well.
Kenzo: The bottom of this well. So the bottom of the well, the riverbank, and where's the third place again?
DM: The plaza.
Kenzo: The plaza in general, okay. Okay.
Kenzo: All right. Communicate that to all the friends.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: so
Kenzo: but, and ju- and just to, you know, 'cause c- communication for like, uh, is what's the, what's the deal with like other, other kind of like life forms?
DM: So there's, there's nothing else alive in the city.
DM: There's nothing that's not part, somehow part of the Ooze that's alive in the city.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: The storm is clearly unnatural.
Unknown: Ugh, okay.
DM: And you can sense that it's growing as well.
Unknown: The storm is-
DM: And it is centered on this like little nodule of Limbo.
Unknown: Ah.
Delwath: Which, the one in...?
DM: At the bottom of the well.
Unknown: Right, okay.
Kenzo: The bottom of the well, plaza, and river.
Unknown: Those are the three-
Unknown: Wait
Unknown: ... those are the three-
Delwath: The bottom of the well and the plaza are two different...
DM: Well, they're just-
Unknown: Okay, okay
Kenzo: ... bottom of the well, like fucking-
DM: Plaza top, bottom of the well, bottom.
Delwath: Okay, okay. But like the, the-
DM: That, well, yes, yes, yeah
Delwath: ... the eye of the storm is where two of the nodules are effectively.
DM: Well, the, the concentration of Ooze matter is on top of the plaza, and then the nodule of Limbo is at the bottom of the well.
Unknown: Okay. Okay.
DM: And then the river is also another high concentration of Ooze matter.
Kenzo: Uh, well, last,
Unknown: we got to figure out-
Unknown: No
Kenzo: ... if we have to fight our way, fight our, fight our way down there.
Unknown: Not first and just-
Kenzo: Just, just, just do it
Unknown: ... get it over with?
Unknown: I mean,
Kenzo: I mean we can go for it and see what happens.
Unknown: Might teleport the
Unknown: brain, see. [laughs]
Kenzo: I know approximately where the nodule is.
Wellby: We could st- are there any of them where there's an easier exit than the other that we could go in and
Wellby: sort of do our exploratory-
DM: Right
Unknown: ... expedition first
DM: ... map a route through the sewers for us-
Unknown: Yeah
Seeker: ... not from the plaza, but from somewhere else.
Delwath: I mean, when did the, when did my double start getting into the...
Delwath: Like how big is the city? Like how far is it from here to the edge of the city?
DM: Uh, that was about... The city of Isengais never, was never a big city, right?
DM: So it's, I don't know,
DM: a-
Unknown: Mile
DM: ... yeah, something like that, right?
DM: It's like not a large... And this, this is, this, the docks are close to the center of the city.
Delwath: Right. So maybe not even. Maybe it's a mile.
DM: Less than a mile.
Delwath: Like a half a mile.
DM: So it's probably half a mile from the edge of the city.
Unknown: [coughs]
DM: The sewers don't extend...
DM: Right, like the storm, Kenzo, would sense this too, the storm extends way beyond the edge of the city itself.
Unknown: Right, right.
DM: And the Ooze, the Ooze is just concentrated in the city, in the sewers below the city.
Delwath: But the, the Ooze didn't seem to react to my...
Delwath: I mean, there's no reaction to my...
Delwath: Do we have any reason to think we would be in danger sneaking into the Ash?
Delwath: I mean, other than the fact that the Ash might have all kinds of bad...
Delwath: I just, if we get closer, we have a lot more options.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: Did we learn anything from defeating the crazy Ash centipede
DM: goblin army thing?
DM: Like the chaos key.
Wellby: That would be relevant here?
DM: Yeah. 'Cause-
Seeker: Didn't we end up using radiant damage against it?
Delwath: No, it was resistant to radiant.
DM: It was resistant to radiant.
Delwath: Can you soul sight the ooze from here?
Delwath: Well, from here, yeah.
Delwath: No, probably not.
Kenzo: Not, not from here, but, um, Tim, I-
DM: From an edge of, from the edge of the sewer you could
Kenzo: Tim, Kenzo will, uh, um, kind of engage the ooze consciousness.
Kenzo: Like I'm gonna, um...
Seeker: Just let it know you're here.
Kenzo: Well, I'm... So basically what I'm kind of curious about is, like...
Kenzo: I- 'cause you kind of asked it, does it have goals?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Right? And it doesn't.
Unknown: No.
Unknown: It did not, right?
Unknown: Okay.
Seeker: But it might wanna go home.
Kenzo: Yeah, so that, that's what... It's like, it's like does it...
Seeker: Is it, is it just, um...
Kenzo: Yeah, I kind of reach out to the ooze consciousness and...
Kenzo: This is sort of like when animals try to like kind of...
Kenzo: Like I, I get close so that like the, the ooze consciousness maybe-
Seeker: It can sniff your hand, yeah.
Unknown: Yeah, exactly.
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: It's kind of like aware that there's like something else there.
Delwath: Do we, do we know it is... Oh, well sorry, finish.
Kenzo: So i- is there like a sensation that the ooze is just like,
Kenzo: is just like kind of reacting and like lashing out and just like...
Kenzo: Or, or is it like,
Kenzo: yeah, is there something there? Is it soothable?
Unknown: Is it like-
DM: So you don't have any sense that it has a...
Unknown: Agency or a?
DM: Uh, yeah. It's not, um...
DM: It's not, it doesn't react to your mind as if, as if, as if it has like conscious will.
Delwath: So like a Limbo slime mold?
DM: It's basically a... Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: It's a Limbo slime mold.
Unknown: Okay. Okay.
DM: Right?
Unknown: Got it. Got it. And then-
Seeker: I was thinking about slime mold, yeah
Kenzo: ... and then the three, the three nodules, like you know like there's that kind of more density.
Kenzo: Like is there a sense that at the more dense nodules, like maybe the consciousness is a little different?
Kenzo: Like is it more intelligent at the nodules, or is it just the whole thing is kind of...
DM: No. It's not.
DM: It just seems... You don't... I mean, it's almost seemed like it was, like a slime mold is, it was really the best way of thinking about it.
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
DM: It's-
Unknown: Okay. Yeah
DM: ...
DM: it's not, um...
DM: It doesn't have the, it doesn't have anything like the sort of sentience and, and sort of will that the Heartroot does, right?
Unknown: Okay.
DM: It's like, but it is like the anti-Heartroot in that it's like a network of these-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah
DM: ... slime tendrils.
DM: But it seems to operate like entirely on instinct, and instinct is just make everything Limbo.
Unknown: Got it.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: the quest- the answer to did it have allies was sort of?
DM: No, the answer to allies was no.
Delwath: Oh, no. Okay.
DM: But that's just because it's all part of a thing.
Kenzo: This is, this is, this is like cancer. You just need to like chemotherapy it and-
Unknown: Right
Kenzo: ... how do we, how do we like nuke the whole thing?
Unknown: Water,
Delwath: magic damage,
Unknown: fire.
Kenzo: Let's go try to destroy one of the nodules and see how it goes.
Unknown: We'll learn a lot.
Wellby: Yeah. We'll start with one.
Kenzo: We'll learn a lot by trying to like-
Unknown: Exactly
Unknown: ... you know.
Seeker: I, I'm wondering if we can send it back to Limbo somehow.
Unknown: But is it...
Delwath: Hmm. The answer of was it from Limbo was sort of.
Unknown: Hmm.
Kenzo: Cool if we could like, talk to it or something, but...
Unknown: Can we show it to the mirror?
Unknown: [laughs] That's interesting.
Unknown: The ooze.
Seeker: In principle, yes.
Delwath: I mean, possibly we could go...
Delwath: We could do a reconnaissance mission to get a piece of it,
Unknown: right?
Seeker: Oh, that's a fun idea.
Delwath: And then like retreat.
Kenzo: I kinda like that. I wanna learn about this thing, 'cause it was like, you know, it's like a little like...
Seeker: How, okay, how are we gonna get some?
Unknown: Hmm.
Delwath: Well, we wanna go to the edge of the city and like enter a sewer or something like that where it's-
Kenzo: Well, it's, it's super reactive. It'll come.
Unknown: It'll, it's gonna-
Unknown: Yeah
Kenzo: ... it's gonna come try to attack us.
Wellby: Yeah. Let's just pick one place and go for it.
Seeker: What is the hazard of walking through the ash?
Unknown: Let's find out.
Kenzo: Uh, can we send something to gauge?
Unknown: [laughs] Kenzo.
Seeker: Someone goes first into the ash to find out what it's like.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: I mean, I have an astral project.
Unknown: You can be astral. Yeah.
Kenzo: Yeah. I'll, I'll, okay, that's fine. Yeah, I'll, I'll, I'll, uh, I'll be an astral, uh...
DM: Just astral project and go as an...
DM: Yeah, okay.
Kenzo: I'll just step into it and see what happens.
Unknown: Um-
Seeker: Oh, oh, oh, we forgot to do Seeker Seven overnight.
Seeker: I mean, we were very tired.
Unknown: Oh, wow.
Seeker: Did we do that? Should we have done that?
Delwath: Wait, and weren't we talking about doing Hero's Feast?
Seeker: We also forgot to do that.
Unknown: Um...
Delwath: But we could...
Delwath: Uh, it's the end of the... I mean, I think it's reasonable.
Delwath: I, here's, here's my suggestion on the plan.
Delwath: We do a reconnaissance. We get a piece of it, right?
Seeker: We can take our time after this.
Delwath: We study it, right?
Delwath: We... There's a few things we can do with the piece of it, right?
Delwath: Like in theory, reconnaissance, Kenzo can so- soul sight it.
Delwath: We can-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah.
Delwath: And then long-
Unknown: Show the mirror. Show the mirror
Delwath: ... and then we'll long rest.
Seeker: Okay. Let's, let's do all that.
Delwath: Right? Before we actually enter, we'll like retreat to somewhere a little bit safe.
Delwath: We'll camp. We'll do a long rest so we can pick one, either Hero's Feast or Seeker Seven.
Seeker: Yeah. Okay.
Unknown: Right.
Seeker: Great. Good idea.
Seeker: Thank you, Tim. Thank you.
Unknown: We do all that.
DM: Okay. So who's... Wait, who's going into the astral?
Unknown: So-
DM: Kenzo astral projection.
Kenzo: I, what's, what's... I'm like, I'm like, I astral, and, and like I stick my pinky in.
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: Well, nothing happens when you stick your pinky in.
Unknown: There's not like a clear edge.
DM: There's not a sharp boundary, right?
DM: It just, on the edge it-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... it just gets increasingly...
DM: What was that?
DM: Dishwasher maybe?
DM: Is the fridge open or is the coffee pot?
Unknown: Coffee?
Unknown: The coffee pot.
DM: Oh, that was the coffee pot turning off.
Wellby: Coffee powering her.
Unknown: The coffee pot is off.
Kenzo: Okay. All right. Kenzo will just walk.
Unknown: Just...
DM: Make a constitution saving throw.
Unknown: Damn it.
Seeker: So there is some hazard of the ash.
Kenzo: When, when, when do, when did, when did I have to make it?
Kenzo: Like what ha- at what point did I get to something that triggered the constitution?
DM: Um, you go in maybe,
DM: uh, it's... Actually, sorry, actually, don't make a constitution saving throw 'cause the first bit of the...
DM: For a while the ash is fairly thin, right?
DM: So it's just... Like you can see it's, it's like lightly obscured.
DM: You can still see a few hundred feet.
DM: You can feel the sort of ash blowing against you.
DM: The winds are sort of very variable, like blowing in all sorts of directions and, um,
DM: but it's like, I mean, like you're...
DM: It's hard to breathe.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: And as you go deeper, as it gets more and more obscured...
Kenzo: So how far have I walked now?
DM: Like maybe a mile.
Kenzo: Oh, shit. Okay.
Kenzo: So I, I'm, I can still tell that, communicate with them.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: I'm giving them a, the whole update.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: So about a mile in, make a constitution saving throw
Kenzo: Uh-oh. 12.
DM: You are poisoned.
Kenzo: Bardic. No, I'm not. I'm immune to poison.
DM: Oh, you are not poisoned.
Kenzo: [laughs] I tell everybody I would've been poisoned if I, if I could be.
DM: You're just choking on the ash, right?
Unknown: Yeah, ash.
DM: It's like toxic.
Kenzo: This sucks. Okay.
Unknown: I come back.
DM: Okay.
Wellby: What did we learn?
Kenzo: Uh, it's poisonous ash. Like you guys will probably choke on it.
Kenzo: I'm immune to poison, but you guys will probably, uh...
Kenzo: So you know, the, the, the, uh, the eye of the storm place where there's no ash, that's a good place to be.
Wellby: Maybe let's go there.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Yeah.
DM: Um,
Delwath: right. But then the ooze will attack us.
Kenzo: So, but if our goal is just to do like a little reconnaissance, then we could just like teleport there,
Kenzo: grab a little ooze.
Delwath: Let it attack us, like cut off a piece of it and flee?
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: Do we all need to go?
Wellby: [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: Well, we need Seeker. He has teleport.
Unknown: Yeah. [laughs] We all need to go.
Seeker: I guess. 'Cause I have like some other shit to do, so hold up.
Delwath: Oh, okay. I have an appointment.
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: Oh my God. Is it Tuesday? [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs] Um, I mean
Delwath: the other option is to-
Wellby: [laughs]
Delwath: The... There's another option here, which is to, to, to, um...
Seeker: I was gonna take a nap, so. [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs] How
DM: about no. Seeker's really ready to settle down.
DM: Yeah, he's been drinking.
Unknown: I know. [laughs]
Wellby: Yeah.
Kenzo: He's like this reluctant golden dragon.
Kenzo: Like [laughs] I think this is like...
Seeker: [laughs] I just had my, my cloak dry cleaned again.
Unknown: I know. [laughs]
Wellby: You just had a vision of like the entire multiverse.
Wellby: Like you just had the most intense trip of your life.
Wellby: That's so true. Right. That's so true.
Wellby: You know? Like-
Unknown: You saw the whole multiverse
Wellby: ... guys, none of this is real, man.
Unknown: Yeah. [laughs] Um,
Delwath: it's poison is the problem?
DM: Yes.
Wellby: It's all self transforming machine elves.
Wellby: Uh...
Unknown: So,
Delwath: uh, green dragons are immune to poison.
Unknown: Interesting.
Wellby: How many of us could be green dragons?
Unknown: Two.
DM: Well, Hero of Ceas makes you immune to poison.
Unknown: Oh.
Wellby: Maybe we could have Hero-
Delwath: Well, so- Hey, hey.
Delwath: That's something ... so, but here's...
Unknown: So
Delwath: we could um,
Delwath: we could do a
Delwath: Kenzo and Delwath.
Delwath: I could turn into a green dragon, Kenzo could ride my back.
Delwath: We could fly in, get a piece of the ooze, and get out.
Seeker: That's cool. I can still soul sight it. Oh, and Wellby and I do really important work back here in the mirror.
Delwath: Like your dad's disappointment. Yeah.
Seeker: That's a, that's a good point.
Wellby: I've got some laundry.
Delwath: [laughs] I mean, that's an immune to poison strategy that works pretty well.
Kenzo: That's true. Yeah. We're both immune to poison.
Kenzo: We roll up, fly through the ash,
Kenzo: go and... Look, I just wanna soul sight it.
Delwath: Soul sighting it would be very useful. Yeah, and I think if we can like swoop down and like take a piece of it
Delwath: somehow. Yeah. We wanna like bring back a piece of the ooze.
Kenzo: That would be cool. Right? And then you could run some tests on it.
Delwath: And then we could run some tests.
Kenzo: Mm-hmm. Love it. Right? Love it. And then, then show it to the mirror.
Kenzo: I wanna show the fucking ooze to the mirror.
Kenzo: It, yeah. Like that's gotta, that's gonna be funny.
Delwath: Because actually we could...
Delwath: Why are we not just...
Delwath: Well, hold on. Here's an even better idea.
Unknown: Um,
Delwath: teleport back to Ventasharna.
Delwath: We'll ra- take a piece of dirt from right here,
Delwath: right? Ah. Then teleport back to Ventasharna.
DM: You can't rainbow bridge. It takes seven days to recharge.
Delwath: Oh, we already used our rainbow bridge.
Delwath: Oh, that's right. Never mind. It's not gonna work.
Delwath: Forget it. Mm-hmm.
Delwath: Nah, it's fine. We'll just fly. Let's take- Okay.
Seeker: Let's do it. Let's do it ... the fly. Yeah.
DM: Okay. Green dragon and Kenzo.
DM: The poison-
Delwath: Delwath turns into a dragon
DM: ... and the dragon.
Delwath: Yes. [laughs] Now only, only Wellby needs to become a dragon.
Delwath: Are you sure you don't wanna be a dragon sometime?
Wellby: I mean, I would love to be.
Kenzo: Th- this is actually kind of a cool thing to be a dragon for 'cause of this.
Wellby: Why not, right?
Unknown: You know? But-
Wellby: Do we wanna burn that...
Wellby: Oh, yeah.
Delwath: I can only tell, t- polymorph one person at a time.
Delwath: Okay. But tomorrow. There's no way a dragon.
Wellby: Is it, uh, is it concentration?
DM: No. No.
Kenzo: No, no, no. I'm riding the dragon. Yeah.
Wellby: Polymorph?
Unknown: Oh, oh, oh, okay, cool. Don't worry. Delwath can do it.
Wellby: I mean, that's just so me and you.
Delwath: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wellby: I'm gonna have better perception-
Unknown: We're, we're gonna be social this episode
Wellby: ... and things too.
Unknown: I'm sure every-
Wellby: If we run into a fight-
Delwath: That's a good idea
Wellby: ... and you wanna polymorph the dragon.
Delwath: No, no, no, no, no. You know what? I should...
Delwath: I'm... No. Change of plan.
Delwath: Sorry. Uh, Wellby's gonna be the dragon.
Delwath: Yes. Right?
Delwath: Because then Delwath won't take any...
Delwath: Like I can maintain concentration.
Delwath: Perfect. Right? Now, here's another question.
Seeker: Um- And you can do
DM: How fast can a dragon fly?
Unknown: Well,
Unknown: uh-
Wellby: So fast.
Seeker: [laughs] Um, the- It's really fast ...
Delwath: the other question here is...
Delwath: Okay, hold on. I'm gonna ask you. A dragon can fly, a green dragon can fly 80,
Delwath: right? So is that close? Are we gonna...
Delwath: But you don't have to go to-
Wellby: Uh, I lose items in polymorph?
Wellby: Do I retain class abilities, like-
DM: No.
Delwath: You retain no abilities.
Delwath: You attain your personality alignment.
Wellby: All right.
Unknown: That's it.
Wellby: But I have wings.
Delwath: Um, but you can fly. 'Cause you're a fucking dragon.
Delwath: Um, but the...
Delwath: We don't have to go to the center.
Wellby: [laughs]
Delwath: They're just trying to find a point where there is ooze.
Seeker: Yeah. They're just trying to get to the surface.
DM: Right, but you have to get, you have to go 14 miles into the storm to get to the edge of the city.
Unknown: That's right. Ah.
DM: Or it's not quite that.
Unknown: So-
DM: It's 13 and a half to the center. You have to go 13 miles into the storm.
Delwath: So let's figure out how far-
DM: So you can go 800 feet a minute.
Delwath: So let's figure out how, and then there's a, I have a question about, um-
Wellby: Wait. Why is the time a problem though?
Unknown: 'Cause-
DM: So that's nine miles per hour.
DM: You're not gonna make it.
Unknown: It's one hour.
Delwath: I mean, you'll be permanently a dragon.
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: How many times can you cast it?
Delwath: Just once, but, but hold on.
Delwath: You can't... Isn't it until dispelled?
DM: Yeah, you, somebody... Seeker could dispel it.
Delwath: Can I just dispel it?
DM: No, y- you need to-
Wellby: You need to dispel magic
DM: ... dispel magic. Someone needs to cast dispel magic.
Delwath: No, no, no, I know. But can I just cast dispel magic-
DM: Yeah
Unknown: ... right when it's cast?
DM: But you don't auto succeed.
DM: It's a ninth level spell, so you have to beat the ability check Unless you cast it with a 9th level slot, which you don't have.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Seeker could cast a spell, magic-
Delwath: Or I could cast like this and then I would auto succeed
DM: ... spell.
Wellby: I mean, we have like bardic inspiration.
DM: [laughs]
Wellby: Like we, there's a-
Unknown: Yeah, you okay with us like...
Wellby: [laughs] Yeah, you okay with that? [laughs]
Seeker: So this is the risk of permanent dragonage.
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: So the question is am I okay with permanently being a giant green dragon?
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Yes. [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: Okay.
Wellby: You should be asking am I okay changing back to a halfling again.
Wellby: [laughs]
Unknown: I mean, um-
Seeker: I mean, I can, I can attest it's an issue.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: At-
Seeker: The changes are jarring.
Unknown: Yeah
Delwath: ... as we, I believe gre- I mean, can't green dragons shape-shift?
DM: But you'll never... You, you have to dispel it in order to get your class abilities back.
Unknown: Yes.
DM: You could shape-shift into a human, but you'd just be a human.
DM: You wouldn't have-
Wellby: Why would I be... I could shape-shift to a halfling.
DM: You could be a halfling.
Unknown: Yes.
Wellby: Yes.
Delwath: Okay. Anyway, if you're okay being a dragon, right, we could just dispel it when you're back.
Delwath: It's fine. No big deal.
Wellby: You don't say that in a way that gives me a great deal of confidence.
Wellby: [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
Delwath: No, you just... Look, it's fine.
Unknown: It'll work.
Delwath: No, no, it'll definitely work.
Wellby: Huh. Look, it's fine. Okay.
Wellby: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's do it.
Kenzo: All right, let's do it.
Wellby: Let's do it.
DM: Okay. So Wellby turns into a dragon.
Unknown: Yes.
DM: Kenzo mounts on the back of the dragon.
Kenzo: Yes. All Merfolk are coming through.
DM: And you begin flying into the ash.
Unknown: [laughs] Yes.
Unknown: Astral-
Wellby: Kenzo, I've, I've had this dream so many times, Kenzo.
Wellby: [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs] Faster. [laughs]
DM: Both of you are immune to poison.
Kenzo: Well, I'm an astral, I'm an astral monk on your-
DM: Well, that only lasts an hour.
Unknown: Oh, yeah.
DM: The astral form.
Unknown: Oh, okay, okay.
DM: Right? As it's gonna take you an hour and a half to get to the edge of the city.
Kenzo: All right. I'll, I'll wait till we get closer to-
DM: So wait till you're a little closer
Unknown: ... yeah.
DM: Um, the sun is also setting, so you can see the, the like
DM: lines of the sunset stretching across, um, the ash cloud from the outside, which is now...
DM: I mean, you guys, you two, um, Delwath and Seeker, are like...
DM: You have the, you have to retreat a bit 'cause the ash is growing stronger, so.
Unknown: Right.
Wellby: Mm.
DM: Um,
DM: you fly 13 miles, an hour and a half, into the storm until you get to the, like
DM: r- roughly the edge of the city.
DM: There's no, there's no real marker, and now this is where the storm is super intense.
DM: Neither of you... I forgot that you're immune to poison, so neither of you have to make con saves because you're both immune to poison.
DM: Um,
DM: and the,
DM: uh... So as you, so as you get...
DM: Like there's no obvious marker that this is the edge of the city or anything, um-
Wellby: But I... No, like I can read the terrain.
DM: Okay. Yeah.
Wellby: Like the shape of the-
DM: Well, the, the visibility's only-
Kenzo: Kenzo knows where the co- Kenzo knows where the consciousness thing is
DM: ... any only 30 feet. Kenzo has a sense, has a memory at least of where the consciousness is.
DM: So you begin flying
DM: around. Like what are you looking for specifically?
Kenzo: Uh, we're, we're, we're trying to find the edge of the, uh, uh, the riverbank, like that area.
Kenzo: We, we wanna chop off a little of the ooze, so we wanna go, kinda go to the edge where the co- the, the edge of the, um,
Unknown: the eye.
DM: Circle?
Kenzo: The eye. The eye.
DM: Oh, you wanna go all the way to the eye?
Kenzo: Well, just where, wherever the ooze is, the edge of the ooze.
DM: Well, there's lots of places you could find, potentially find the ooze.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: 'Cause it stretch... Remember it stretches all underneath the city.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
DM: So that's why I know... I mean, the,
DM: the plaza in the middle is the easiest place, but I just want to know what you want to look for specifically.
Unknown: I mean, I think, uh-
DM: Like are you looking for a different well?
DM: Are you looking for a sewer outlet into the river?
DM: Are you just going to the plaza?
Kenzo: I, I think, I think as we're flying, we're headed...
Kenzo: Well, let's head towards the plaza.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: But as we're going, if there's any other like little thing where it looks like there's a bit of ooze that's coming out-
Wellby: Yeah
Kenzo: ... then we, we can stop there. We're, our...
Kenzo: This is mission collect ooze.
DM: Okay.
Kenzo: That's what, that, that's our mission right here.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So-
Seeker: Look for wells. Yeah
DM: ... make a, make a perception check with disadvantage because you're, it's having, it's, it's obscured.
Wellby: Uh, do I have advantage from the bow-
Unknown: You have blind sense now
Wellby: ... that cancels the disadvantage?
DM: No, 'cause you can't use equipment in dragon form.
Wellby: Um, oh, that's right.
Delwath: But do you have... Does blind sense help?
Delwath: Blind sense can see through obscured things.
DM: Oh, as the dragon, that makes sense.
Delwath: Dragon has 60 foot blind sense at 113.
DM: Okay. So-
Wellby: 13, 11. It's still above 25
Wellby: ... straight forward. Yeah.
DM: Um,
DM: right. I guess, well,
DM: yeah, yeah. Well, right.
DM: You get your-
Wellby: Well, uh-
DM: ... dragon bonus, not the-
Wellby: Oh
DM: ... You don't have reliable talent or your-
Wellby: Yes.
Unknown: Although-
Wellby: Do I add my proficiency bonus?
Delwath: Nope. Uh, you add the dragon's, which is the same as yours.
Wellby: Does someone have that h-
Delwath: Yeah, I got it. I got it. Perception plus 12.
Wellby: Uh, that's a 23 was the worst of the two rolls.
DM: Okay. So as you're, as you're approaching,
DM: um, you do see, like you sense with your blind sense because you can sort of, um, sense the layout of the ground below you as you're, you're approaching.
DM: There's not, there's not a well that you pass, but you see like a, there's like a collapsed well basically that once was a well, but that's fallen in.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: And there's a ring of rubble around the outside.
DM: So theoretically you could
DM: try there or you could just keep going.
Wellby: What do you think?
Unknown: Just try there.
Wellby: Let's do it.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Okay.
DM: So you land.
Wellby: Yes.
Kenzo: Uh, Kenzo senses where the ooze, touch this.
DM: It's, it's right below you.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Doesn't seem to have sensed you yet.
Kenzo: There, there is a well here.
DM: Uh, yes.
Unknown: Like a-
DM: Like partially full of rubble.
Wellby: So I thought we were gonna like sneak in and chop off a piece of the ooze and-
Unknown: Yeah
Wellby: ... bring it back.
Kenzo: Yeah. Basically, yeah.
Kenzo: Uh, okay. Well, if it's, there's rubble, that's fine.
Kenzo: K- uh, Kenzo passes through it.
DM: Okay. So Kenzo begins dropping down through the, through the rubble in the well.
Wellby: If I shape-shift, do I retain my poison immunity or do I take on the, um-
Unknown: Oh, good question
Wellby: ...
Wellby: whatever I shift into?
Unknown: Uh-
DM: Uh, dragon-
Unknown: I don't...
Unknown: Okay
DM: ... like adult green dragon doesn't have shape-shift.
Delwath: Yeah, except we fought a green dragon and he had shape-shift, which is...
Delwath: I never, I didn't actually look at the stats.
DM: Oh.
Delwath: I just assumed the dragon could shape-shift.
DM: Yeah, yeah. No, no, no, because the o- the...
DM: Interesting.
DM: The, the old green...
DM: Yeah, yeah. Fine. Dragon can shape-shift.
Delwath: I, I only assumed it could shape-shift because we fought a shape-shifting green dragon.
DM: The-
Seeker: [gentle music] So may- I mean, maybe we can't, I
Delwath: just, I just was operating on the
Delwath: in world rather than stat block
DM: Right, but not every dream dragon has the same abilities.
Unknown: Yeah, no, that's-
DM: No, that's fair
Delwath: ... yeah, it's fair.
DM: Yeah.
Delwath: Totally fair.
DM: Yep.
Delwath: I, I just... That's why I said it could shape shift.
Wellby: I think there's something exciting to Kenzo going alone.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
DM: So, so drops down through the-
Unknown: Um, y'all
DM: ... through the-
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: ... through the rubble, and you s-
DM: ... you come to what looks like,
DM: um,
DM: a,
DM: a partially collapsed
DM: cistern, right? Like, it seems like there was, um...
DM: What is that, what is that place in
DM: Istanbul I wanna see that-
Unknown: Oh, oh
DM: ... say was, uh-
Unknown: Where's the, um,
Seeker: Medusa heads. It's up, there's like an upside down Medusa head inside the Basilica Cistern, it's called.
DM: Yeah, yeah. The Basilica Cistern.
Seeker: It's a crazy fucking place.
DM: That's what I'm,
DM: that's what I'm, uh...
DM: So I don't know if you guys know this.
Wellby: I don't know it. Describe it.
DM: So the Basilica Cistern-
Seeker: I've been, yeah
DM: ... is a massive cistern, um,
DM: that was built in
DM: Constantinople-
Unknown: A thousand years ago
DM: ... in the, in the third to fourth century, and was like a huge...
DM: It's like a giant underwater,
DM: underground cistern-
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... that's, like, has all sorts of rows of,
DM: um, like columns and pillars and, um, it m- it looks super cool from the pictures.
DM: Um, and that's basically what is beneath Isingue.
DM: Or at least this part of Isingue, is this massive underground
DM: cistern with wells that go d- that drop down into it from different parts of the city, and clearly fed by the river.
Unknown: Mm.
DM: Um,
DM: and you see that...
DM: But it's, but it, like a lot of it has collapsed, so while once in the heyday of Isingue it would've been this massive open space, now, like, there's just
DM: collapsed ceilings and limes.
DM: So it's not actually a sewer system that the ooze lives in, it's the, the network that's created by the piles of rubble that now block large parts
DM: of the system-
Unknown: Ooh, whoa
DM: ... creating a maze.
DM: But you see below you, um, two small, two, like, tendrils of greenish purple, um,
DM: ooze-like substance
DM: that turn and see you, and leap to attack.
Unknown: Nice.
Wellby: How's it going down there, Kenzo?
Kenzo: Uh, so far so good. Initiative?
DM: Yep.
Unknown: 24.
DM: Yeah, you move then.
Seeker: Um, Kenzo will, uh,
Kenzo: yeah, Kenzo will... 'Cause this is, this is mission capture ooze, so, um,
Kenzo: he's gonna try to, um,
Kenzo: like literally just go and, I don't know if it's grappling or what it would be, but, like, he literally wants to go and just with magic hands, like, tear some of these off.
DM: So,
DM: so grapple, I mean, if you stun one you could just, like, grab it.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Um, you could try grappling and then use a, like an object interaction to try and rip a piece off,
DM: um-
Delwath: Soul sight it first? Oh, yeah.
Kenzo: Soul sight, thank you.
Kenzo: Soul sight first then.
DM: Um-
Unknown: First things first.
DM: [laughs] Okay.
DM: So...
Unknown: [laughs] Is it friendly?
DM: No, it's not friendly. Um, the-
Unknown: Oh, hang on.
DM: The ooze is...
DM: Um, I don't know how to-
Seeker: I can take a look at some pictures there, but
DM: ... we're trying to figure out the best way to actually-
Seeker: This is, this is my picture of the upside down Medusa head.
Seeker: What? And there is the s- interior of the- Oh, I can imagine ...
Seeker: cistern. Yeah.
Seeker: It's just a crazy place. Like it's- Those things are so cool ...
Seeker: all dark. There's just like an exten- expanse of water for like a football field.
DM: Yeah.
Seeker: And there's just ancient columns in rows- Wow ...
Seeker: going on forever. [laughs] I feel like- It's crazy [laughs] ...
Wellby: ancient civil engineering is amazing.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So, um,
DM: the... [laughs] So here, here's how soul sight's gonna work, because each part of the ooze is also, has a different stat box.
Unknown: Oh, my gosh.
DM: So you're gonna get-
Unknown: Okay
DM: ... a little bit of information about this part of the ooze, and a little bit of information about the whole, the basic ooze.
DM: Um, so you, so this, this, uh,
DM: um,
DM: purple pseudopod
DM: is CR 9.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: Resistant to acid.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Immune to blinded, charmed, deafened, exhausted, frightened, prone, prone.
DM: Um,
DM: bad at charisma, good at strength.
Unknown: Well.
DM: Um, this is a small piece of the actual ooze itself, and you get just, like, one piece of information about the full ooze from soul sighting
DM: a segment. So what do you want to know about the full ooze?
DM: One of the things.
Unknown: Right.
DM: Resistances, immunities, strongest save, weakest save, or CR.
DM: You can pick one.
Unknown: Immunities.
Unknown: Weakest save.
DM: Well, pick one.
Kenzo: Hmm. Life story. Well, we're gonna get that once we, uh, strip it here.
DM: [laughs]
Wellby: Closest friends, deepest fear. [laughs]
Unknown: Favorite movies. Um [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
Wellby: Um, yeah, I'll go with, I'll go with immunities. Favorite date.
DM: Acid, necrotic, poison damage.
DM: Charmed, exhausted, frightened, grappled, paralyzed, petrified, poisoned, prone, restrained, stunned, and unconscious.
Kenzo: That sounds like one of those, like, uh, it's like a Joseph's multicolored coat or something.
Wellby: Yeah. The, those are all of its immunities?
DM: Yeah.
Seeker: Read them again. Are there things that it's not immune to, jeez.
Wellby: Uh, would that be quicker? [laughs]
DM: Yeah. Actually I don't think there's any conditions it's not immune to.
Unknown: Oh, it's immune to all the conditions.
DM: Oh, incapac- It's not immune to incapacitated then
Kenzo: It can't be blinded, but it could be tripped?
DM: It's immune to prone
Wellby: It's too big to be tripped
DM: It's immune to charmed, exhaustion, frightened, grappled, paralyzed, petrified, poisoned, prone, restrained, stunned, unconscious
Delwath: So yeah, it's basically immune to all conditions
Unknown: Wow
Unknown: And what kind of damage? Acid
DM: Acid, necrotic, and poison damage
Kenzo: Wow. Okay, cool. I, uh, I, uh, attack it and take a bit of it
DM: Okay, make an attack roll
Seeker: Just gonna like smack a piece of it off with their staff
Kenzo: Uh, I've got magic hands. Let's try to like break a freak a piece off
Seeker: Hmm. Just scoop out a chunk
Unknown: That's 13.
Kenzo: Oh, actually maybe I'll, maybe I'll hit it with my staff first.
Unknown: I'll try to break a-
DM: Okay
Kenzo: ... piece off with my staff. It's a plus 15.
Unknown: Uh, 27
DM: Yeah, that hits
Kenzo: Now what do I do? Can I... How can I like-
DM: So, well, if you wanna, if you wanna actually break a piece off, you have to first grapple it and then rip it it, rip the piece in half.
DM: I was just suggesting earlier, if you stun it, it will automatically fail.
Delwath: You'll automatically be able to grapple it
Kenzo: All right. So then I, then I, uh, I, I stun it.
Kenzo: I try to stun it
DM: Okay. So it needs to make a DC 20 con save.
DM: That is a 16
Unknown: It fails
DM: So it is stunned
Kenzo: Great. And now I can...
DM: I mean, you can flurry of blows.
DM: So grappling is an unarmed attack
Unknown: Yeah
DM: So just make an unarmed attack.
DM: You have advantage on the attack roll
Unknown: Oh, shit.
Unknown: Uh,
Delwath: uh, oh, I have a plus 14 now.
Unknown: Uh, 19?
DM: 19 hits
Unknown: Okay
DM: So you grapple it, and then just as a, because it's stunned, as a free object interaction, you can rip a piece off
Kenzo: Perfect. Great. And now I will, uh, disengage and run
Kenzo: But you don't have any actions. You don't have any-
DM: You use your bonus action. You can just run, but it's stunned, so it can't do anything
Kenzo: Okay, perfect. I get out of there
DM: Okay. Well done
Unknown: Nice
DM: Good job
Delwath: See, you didn't really need to break it
Unknown: off
DM: So you run
Kenzo: We didn't all have to go
DM: There's this-
Unknown: [laughs] Right
DM: ... this. So as you pull the piece of ooze off, it hardens into crystal
Unknown: Ooh
Unknown: Crystal. That's cool
Unknown: Okay, great
DM: And then you flee back up the tunnel before the collapse, away from the-
Unknown: Yes
DM: ... ruined cistern
Kenzo: And then I hop back on Wellby's back, and then we fly back to the, where everybody else is
Unknown: Yeah
Wellby: Yeah
Kenzo: And then the dispel does not work, and Wellby stays a green dragon forever
Wellby: [laughs]
DM: The end
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: Well, I mean-
Wellby: Wa- has it been an hour?
DM: Oh, it's been more than an hour
Unknown: How's it feel, Wellby? It's been-
Wellby: I've got some real life choices right now
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Well, Wellby-
Wellby: Yeah
Kenzo: ... w- what are... W- w- so what do you think now that you've had the experience?
Wellby: Uh, I mean, the flying part feels pretty normal.
Wellby: It's the, uh... it's just the size.
Wellby: Like, I, I should be able to fit through things and I can't
Kenzo: Yeah, yeah, yeah. Pretty different, right?
Wellby: Like, I can touch both sides of the deck at the same time.
Wellby: I've been trying to-
Unknown: I, I know what you're talking about
Wellby: Look at this. Look at this
Unknown: You're great. I just-
Wellby: I'm touching them both
Seeker: ... I just had that yesterday. That's so-
Seeker: Pretty great. Yeah, yeah
Unknown: ... weird. I mean...
Kenzo: Ah, if only we all could feel that, wow, it feels like to be a dragon
Wellby: Mm-hmm
Unknown: Totally
Unknown: Yeah.
Kenzo: Well, guess there's no way.
Wellby: It's been a good run, though. I feel ready to go back to being-
Unknown: Halfling
Wellby: ... halfling again.
Unknown: All right.
Kenzo: Do you cast dispel magic or anyone down here?
Unknown: Oh, I cast dispel magic
Unknown: I mean-
DM: Anybody can
Wellby: ... I'm sort of like, like dysphoria [laughs]
Unknown: Hmm.
Unknown: Right?
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: Um-
Seeker: Wing dysphoria
Delwath: ... dys- to dispel an ninth level spell, though, you have to roll a 14 or higher for s- assuming, assuming you have a plus five
DM: Yeah, you have, you have to roll a 14 or higher with dispel magic
Seeker: And there's just this one
Unknown: chance ever?
Unknown: No
DM: Oh, no, you add half your...
DM: Oh, no, yeah, 14 or higher
Delwath: I mean, I could auto succeed by casting glyph it
DM: You can just... I mean, it's a third level slot.
DM: You can just try a few times, and if it doesn't work, you can use a fourth level slot and then a fifth level slot
Unknown: Oh, okay
DM: You're planning on resting, right?
Unknown: Yeah, yeah
DM: So-
Delwath: Yeah. But if we're planning on resting, I should just do glyph and-
DM: Do glyph and
Delwath: ... uh, I'll just, I'll just-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah
Delwath: ... Delwath will just dispel it. Well-
DM: Okay
Delwath: ... I'll try... Nah, I'll just do it
Wellby: You'll su- you'll succeed
Unknown: I'll just do it
Unknown: Yeah
Delwath: Okay. I'll auto succeed
Unknown: We show the, uh, uh-
DM: Hmm
Unknown: ... ooze to Beryl
DM: Okay
Wellby: Yeah
Unknown: Amazing
Wellby: Yeah, yeah
Seeker: And what's our question?
Delwath: What's our question? Um, wait, wait.
Delwath: First, is it a creature of Limbo?
Delwath: My sword can detect creatures of Limbo
DM: Oh, yeah. Uh...
Unknown: Sword
DM: N- no
Unknown: No
DM: Well, hmm.
DM: No, it is not a creature. It is not a native-
Unknown: That-
DM: It is not native to Limbo
Seeker: That it turned into crystal is very interesting because that's the antithesis of Limbo.
Seeker: Crystal is the kind of epitome of order, isn't it?
Unknown: So maybe-
DM: True
Seeker: ... it's a corrupted creature from...
Seeker: What's the plane of order called?
Unknown: Machinus?
Unknown: Mechanus
Unknown: Mechanus.
Seeker: Maybe it's a sort of like imprisoned victim of the war in Mechanus thousands of years ago-
DM: Hmm
Delwath: ... that has been Limbo-fied.
Seeker: Anyway, why would it turn into crystal?
Unknown: It's, it's odd
Wellby: That is odd
Unknown: It is odd
Seeker: Or maybe that's just a collapsed state of Limbo entities where-
Wellby: [coughs]
Seeker: ... organized life from the material plane
Seeker: turns into ooze when it dies,
Unknown: and
Seeker: ooze when it dies turns into-
Wellby: How did you-
Unknown: ... something perfectly organized.
Unknown: But that's the reverse-
Wellby: There's something to that
Seeker: ... right, reverse entropy state from its living state
Kenzo: Tim, uh, once I pull the piece of ooze off, can I, can I, can I touch this?
DM: In your hand? No
Kenzo: It's, it's like dead
DM: Dead, yeah
Seeker: What... Is it a black opaque crystal or-
DM: It's more like sort of purple-gray.
DM: It's like purple-y with gray and swirly streaks
Unknown: Amethyst-y
DM: Sort of amethyst-y, but dull.
DM: It doesn't have, it doesn't glint It's not like...
Unknown: It's not magical?
DM: N- well, not only that it's not magical, it's that it, it feels a little, it looks a little desaturated.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
DM: Like, it's not, it's not the sort of vibrant sort of bright gemstone.
DM: It's a
DM: grayish purple sort of desaturated hue.
Seeker: Is there any arcane meaning to
Seeker: grayish purple desaturated hue?
DM: No.
Kenzo: All right, let's show it the mirror.
DM: Yep.
Wellby: Yeah.
Kenzo: And we ask it, um...
Kenzo: Should we ask it what, what's its story?
Seeker: How to defeat it?
Kenzo: What are your... What's its weaknesses?
Wellby: How... Like, how did it come to being in grow- like...
Delwath: I mean, the story of its growth?
Kenzo: Well, we kinda wanna know two things. I mean, we wanna know its story just for fun and just for plot, but we also really wanna know how to kill it.
Wellby: Well, but I'm thinking that too, like maybe knowing how it came into being offers some-
Unknown: Yeah
Wellby: ... clue to its-
Delwath: I think its origins will offer-
Wellby: ... undoing
Delwath: ... clues 'cause the mirror doesn't tell us, like...
Wellby: Yeah.
Unknown: Strategies.
Wellby: Strategies.
Unknown: Right. Yeah.
Seeker: Okay. All right. I, I think the story of, uh, its life.
Kenzo: Tell us how you came to be. Tell, tell us how you came to be.
DM: Yeah. Make a wisdom check.
Unknown: Yes.
DM: And the most-
Unknown: Plus six
Seeker: ... exciting attack of a sky ship thing ever
Kenzo: Wait, plus six? Isn't it plus a billion?
DM: Perfect.
Wellby: [laughs]
DM: No, it's just a straight wisdom check, just wisdom, plus your wisdom mods, so plus six.
Unknown: Dang it. 19.
DM: Okay, that's... Um, so you hold it up to the mirror.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: And you watch as the
DM: image in the mirror turns briefly black, and then
DM: you see
DM: below you,
DM: uh, sort of looking up, just one sort of, uh, circle of light above the sun shining down into a,
DM: uh, dark-
Kenzo: Which sun? Which sun?
DM: The, the Material Plane sun.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: Shining down into a, um...
DM: Y- you can see, like, ripples in the water, right?
DM: So you're... It's, like, looking down into this cistern below Isengay, uh, but when it is less ruined.
DM: And then there's a
DM: viol- like, the... Everything starts shaking like an earthquake and...
DM: But instead of things falling down, there's, like,
DM: things that jut out that are shooting out from the ground, like pieces of stone.
DM: Water is, like, solidifying and shooting up as a spike of solid water.
DM: The, some of the stones are beginning to, like, decay at the bottom and melt and, like, flow out across like liquid stone-
Unknown: Sounds pretty Lim-
DM: ... across the surface
Kenzo: ... sounds, sounds pretty Limbo.
Seeker: This is the rupture event.
DM: And then, um, there's a,
DM: uh...
DM: The wa- the water itself in the...
DM: Oh, that's a detail I forgot to mention.
DM: So there's, there was...
DM: Essentially, you saw essentially no water in the cistern.
Unknown: Mm. Mm.
DM: You didn't actually see any water down below.
Kenzo: Mm. Mm. Mm. Oh, shit.
DM: The wa- you see, you see, like, a,
DM: a dark,
DM: uh, swirling mass of, like, liquid stone and, uh,
DM: uh...
DM: I don't know how to describe it. Like, threads, like, like if you took, if you took a...
DM: If you took, like, a bunch of gummy bears and y- or sorry, gummy worms, and microwaved them slightly so they're all, like-
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah
DM: ... stuck together into a-
Wellby: Gelatinous mass
DM: ... gelatinous mass.
DM: It nucleates in the center of the water underneath the cistern.
DM: [phone ringing]
Kenzo: This is so crazy. I haven't heard a phone ring in, like,
Unknown: 20 years.
DM: Um.
Unknown: You guys...
DM: It's always Sam.
Unknown: Oh, okay, okay.
Delwath: Yeah, if it was, like, somebody who needs to reach me, they can call me or something.
DM: Right. Um, and then this gelatinous mass, uh,
DM: hardens into solid stone.
DM: Yeah, it's all Sam. And then, and then, like, um,
DM: it... The, like, nearest bit of the water begins to, like, solidify into jelly, and you watch over time as more and more bits of the water underneath
DM: Isengay, like little filaments will form, stretching out across the water and, like, solidify and crystallize and nucleate along that filament, emerging from this,
DM: this mass at the center which then begins to spin and actually splits into two that are connected by some wire, like, orb- orbiting
DM: around each other with...
DM: Like, as they spin, s- throwing off more and more little filaments that land further in the water, and then a line of, like, gelatinous mass, like, nucleates along the line.
Delwath: Oh, boy. So wait, this is two...
DM: There's two of these, like, solid masses of microwaved gummy worms-
Unknown: Right
DM: ... that have solidified and turned into some kind of weird...
Delwath: What is that muttering about?
Wellby: I don't know.
DM: Um.
Unknown: Still talking.
DM: The, um... They're spinning around each other, and as they spin, they're throwing off more little bits that nucleate into another...
Kenzo: So yeah, so th- this is totally gonna, like, like...
Kenzo: Th- this is literally, um, the fucking...
Kenzo: It's the great, it's the great ooze, the, the, the, uh, nanotechnology feared thing.
Wellby: Oh.
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Wellby: The Gray Goo.
DM: But-
Unknown: This is literally the-
Delwath: But we only detected one.
DM: Well,
DM: I mean...
Delwath: They could have clumped together.
DM: Yeah, or, like, there's t- there's two tendrils orbiting around each other, but they're one...
Unknown: Spot.
Wellby: Spot, right.
DM: Spot, right.
Kenzo: But the, but the thing that... It's, it's, it's, it's, it's water that's, like, causing it to...
Kenzo: It's, like, infecting water and then...
DM: Yeah, it's infecting all of the water underneath Isengay.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: And then all of that is, like, solidifying and drawing in.
DM: And you watch... Like, time has sped up in the mirror, right?
DM: So you watch over time-
Unknown: Mm-hmm
DM: ... as more and more of these...
DM: And then the first, like, maybe years later, there's the first little...
DM: It's slow. It's a slow process.
DM: You know, the, the first little tendril creeps up out of, uh-
DM: ... out of a well and like begins to feel around
Unknown: Yeah
DM: Right? And at this point that you can see in the mirror, right, Isingue is much more intact, but over time it begins to corrode and destroy all of the...
DM: It seems to actually eat the stone somehow.
DM: It's like acidically corroding all of the stone in the city as it slowly grows over years.
DM: I mean, it's been growing for a quite a long time.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: All right.
Unknown: So-
Wellby: What does that suggest for how to destroy it?
Delwath: Find the little nodule thing, right?
Delwath: I mean, it's what the plan kind of suggested at the very beginning.
Delwath: Find its center and then-
Wellby: Starting point
Unknown: I mean,
Delwath: we know where it is. We just have to fight our way...
Delwath: I mean, the naive thing is we fight our way to the nodule and then we
Delwath: do something clever.
Kenzo: Well, what would be cool is if there was a way to like, if there was like an antidote.
Kenzo: Like what's the anti-limbo antidote to like kind of decontaminate it, like the bioremediation strategy?
Delwath: Right. To like, like cause it to shrink and draw back and-
Unknown: Yeah
Delwath: ... retreat out of the city. So
Kenzo: Yeah, exactly. Exactly.
Kenzo: That would be cool.
Kenzo: The dumber thing feels like we just like go and
Wellby: Drop down in
Unknown: Yeah
Delwath: It's like do we try and,
Delwath: do we try and like
Delwath: make it withdraw into itself and get smaller, and smaller, and smaller, or do we just go kill the brain?
Kenzo: Uh, yeah, 'cause it's like how do we get down to the bottom of the where the, the third, the third one thing?
Kenzo: That, that... It's the one at the v- very bottom that's like the, you know-
Unknown: Right
Kenzo: ... probably the main one.
Unknown: Mm.
Unknown: I mean
Wellby: It grew up in the sewer?
DM: Well, the sister.
Unknown: The sister.
Wellby: The sister. Maybe it doesn't like light?
Unknown: Oh.
Wellby: Like maybe it wants to be in the dark.
Delwath: I think it, I think that it likes the water.
Unknown: It's more water.
Delwath: I think it's more that it spread...
Delwath: This may be slightly cheating, but I...
Delwath: The water of, of
Delwath: Isingue, I think it spread along.
DM: Yeah, no, you knew that from the Heartroot.
Delwath: Right. Okay. Wait, we knew the water's magical.
Wellby: Yeah. So can like we starve it of its water somehow?
Unknown: Or, or desiccate it
Unknown: Yeah
Seeker: Like maybe with heat we can dry it out.
Delwath: I think it's... Doesn't it, isn't the water all gone now?
DM: The water's all gone, but there's clear- there was a Kenza sensed a concentration in the river.
DM: The river is not dry.
Delwath: Oh, maybe we go kill the river one.
Unknown: And then there's-
Seeker: And then it will no longer have a source of water
Delwath: It disconnects it from the magic.
Delwath: Maybe that's how we bioremediate it, right?
Delwath: In other words, if it's-
Kenzo: Mm. Yeah. All right. Let's do that
Delwath: ... if it's growing from the...
Delwath: And the nice thing about the water one
Unknown: Outside
Delwath: Outside and also like, I mean, I don't want to copy Seeker, but two leviathans?
Unknown: [laughs]
Seeker: Two leviathans
Delwath: Water creatures
Seeker: Good movement speed in like in the river.
Seeker: Interesting point you're making.
Kenzo: Let's do it. Let's go kill the river one.
Delwath: Like, there's a certain appeal in like let's...
Delwath: Like we could like go after it in the river and then-
Kenzo: Let's do it. Long rest and then what do we do?
Kenzo: Are you making another Seeker? Are we doing a Hero's Feast?
Wellby: Yeah. Load up all the things.
Unknown: Load up all the-
Delwath: Well, we can only do one
Seeker: Probably Hero's Feast.
Unknown: Oh, no.
Delwath: Oh, no, 'cause you didn't take Hero's Feast as a spell.
Unknown: Right.
Seeker: But what did I end up taking? I know I took-
Delwath: You took Demiplane
Unknown: Oh
Delwath: So you can only Hero's Feast by casting Wish.
Unknown: Oh.
Delwath: You can still cast Hero's Feast as Wish.
Unknown: Okay. Yeah
Unknown: Didn't you take Demiplane?
Unknown: Um.
Unknown: That's what we talked about. We talked about-
Unknown: Yeah
Delwath: ... taking Demiplane.
Seeker: Yeah, you're right.
Kenzo: Well, that, that's what we all suggested, but I don't know.
Kenzo: Eric chose it.
Seeker: Quickly now
Unknown: But [laughs]
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: I mean, if you had Hero's Feast you could do a Sumacrum and Hero's Feast.
Unknown: But-
DM: Well, the down, the biggest downside to a Sumacrum is it takes 12 hours to cast which means that-
Delwath: Not unless you cast it with Wish
DM: ... unless you cast it with Wish.
Wellby: And then that's the Wish.
Seeker: Is there some reason to think that would be especially helpful?
Unknown: Sumacrum?
Delwath: No, only like
Delwath: it's, it's a good... It's your last opportunity for a Seeker 7.
Delwath: Well, Seeker 7 can come with us and Frank.
DM: Seeker, Seeker 7 can come with you to the Plane of Fire.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: I, I think Hero's Feast...
DM: It's gonna be tough if you're all constantly poisoned
Delwath: And Hero's Feast is definitely-
DM: Poison gives you disadvantage on all tests
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: So I-
Unknown: Yeah
Seeker: ... I use Wish to cast Hero's Feast and then you're immune to poison.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Then you're immune to poison for 24 hours.
DM: So you cast it right before you go to bed so you're im- immune to poison all the next day.
Unknown: Right
Seeker: And I get my Wish slot back
DM: And you get your Wish slot back, yeah.
Unknown: Let's do that.
Delwath: Perfect. And I mean, I guess if you didn't want to use Wish, but I don't think Seeker 7 is your best option for...
Delwath: Like you're probably better using Wish to turn into a leviathan or something like that.
Delwath: Or sorry, using Shape Shift to turn into a leviathan.
Seeker: That's what I'm gonna do the next day, yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Delwath: But I mean, I'm, I'm pretty tempted to do the same thing.
Unknown: Yeah. Are you-
Delwath: If we're going in the river
Unknown: Yeah, we're going in the river
Delwath: ... there, there's something to be said for...
Delwath: Especially it's not a... If there's no Creatures of Limbo here, so I don't get 4d8 damage, I only get 2d8 damage
Unknown: Right
Delwath: It makes, uh...
Unknown: So
DM: here Seeker...
DM: As the sun sets you set up camp.
DM: Seeker creates a feast for you
DM: and you
DM: consume the feast. Roll 2d10.
DM: Everybody gets 2d10 added to your hit point maximum.
Unknown: Nice.
Delwath: Can you stack that with Aid, by the way?
DM: There's, yeah, no reason not.
DM: They're different spells.
Unknown: Okay.
DM: No, Seeker rolls 2d10.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: For everybody.
Unknown: Oh, excuse me.
DM: Everybody gets the same amount.
Unknown: Right.
Unknown: 11.
Unknown: Solid.
DM: So everybody adds 11 to their hit point maximum.
DM: Uh, we're not in Vinasharna though, right?
DM: You're not in Vinasharna.
Delwath: We could be though, right?
Seeker: Wait, where did you add it? Where did I add it?
Kenzo: Seeker has two teleports Is this temporary hit points or is this like when you create increase the maximum?
DM: No, it's if you go to the, um,
DM: the-
Unknown: Because if we-
Delwath: Override max, I see it. Got it
Delwath: ... if we long rest in Vinasharana we can get a billion and a half.
Seeker: [coughs] It's the max HP modifier, right?
DM: But that's if you're planning on polymorphing that's the most useful-
Kenzo: Uh, there's a thing that says override max HP
DM: ... to check if you go away the minimum
Seeker: Oh, that's true. Looks... That's true. [clears throat] It must be the max HP modifier.
DM: Max H... Set max HP modifier to 11.
Unknown: To 11. [keyboard clacking]
Unknown: Okay. [paper rustling] And
Delwath: then actually set it to everybody-
Unknown: You get 20 more?
Delwath: Gets 20 more except somebody.
Delwath: I guess Seeker normally doesn't get the extras from anybody.
DM: So-
Unknown: Okay
DM: ... Wellby and-
Unknown: So 31
DM: ... Kenso set it to 31.
Delwath: And Delwath.
DM: And Delwath.
Unknown: Nice. Nice.
Unknown: Nice.
DM: Nice.
Unknown: And you are-
Seeker: Do you still like it? Okay, I said that on the character sheet.
Wellby: Yep, I'll get there in a minute.
DM: You are immune to the frightened and poisoned conditions.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: You have resistance to poison damage.
Unknown: [paper rustling] Okay.
Seeker: I think we did the right thing. [paper rustling] And now we dream of very fish.
Delwath: Are you changing your sword?
Delwath: Oh, yes. I am changing my sword.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: probably to [paper rustling]
Unknown: Arboria.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: I think, I think,
Unknown: um-
DM: Mechanist and Arboria
Delwath: ... I think Mechanist and Arboria [paper rustling] 'cause Pandemonium is not likely to be useful.
Wellby: The Pandemonium gives psychic damage.
Wellby: So, no, it... No, you, they do have resistance to psychic damage.
Delwath: Oh, that could be useful actually.
Delwath: Um, actually,
Delwath: [paper rustling] I might do that instead.
Delwath: I'm gonna do that.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: It also gives me advantage on saving throws against possession so that's not worth it.
Unknown: [coughs]
DM: Yes.
DM: [coughs] Okay. So
DM: the morning comes, uh, the a- you've, you set up camp about a mile from the ash storm and it's now spread so that the edges of the storm are
DM: l- are lapping up [object thuds] against your tents.
Unknown: Oh, boy.
DM: As you wake from the, a nice rest, refreshed with your heroes' feast.
Delwath: Everybody gets certified inspiration.
Delwath: With your inspiration, your extra hit points [paper rustling] everything.
Unknown: Sweet.
DM: So you're now, you are now maybe
DM: 50, f- 15 miles from the
DM: plaza as the storm has grown slightly.
DM: Grew a couple miles over the course of the night.
DM: [gentle music] And where are you heading?
Unknown: River.
Seeker: Up river, outside the storm.
DM: Well, the river's the... Oh, go to the river outside the storm and then travel upriver till you get to...
Seeker: Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
DM: Yeah.
Kenzo: You guys are returning the leviathan. That's cool.
DM: Yeah, I think, yeah.
Unknown: Sweet.
Delwath: I feel a little derivative here, but I think it's the right choice.
Unknown: I mean, it's a team effort.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: There you go. [paper rustling] Two leviathan is better than one leviathan.
Unknown: That's true.
DM: That is a true statement.
Wellby: As the saying goes.
Unknown: [laughs] Um, can-
Kenzo: Can, can there be three leviathans?
Unknown: No.
DM: No, not in a fight.
Unknown: It's not powerful though.
Wellby: Three leviathans are not better than two.
Unknown: Oh, I never found out what that was.
Kenzo: I don't know where the stat block-
Wellby: As the saying goes.
DM: You do have a scroll of wish.
Kenzo: [laughs] There could be three leviathans.
Unknown: There could be three leviathans.
DM: But you can't use wish to cast a 9th level spell.
Unknown: Correct.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Um-
Seeker: 341 HP. [paper rustling] Wait, this must be a different leviathan 'cause it has a 40-foot swim.
Unknown: [paper rustling]
Wellby: Is it the old, uh...
Seeker: I don't know, man. Where, where do I...
Seeker: Where should I find the stat block?
Delwath: Tim's gonna send it to you.
DM: Yeah, let me find-
Delwath: It has-
Unknown: Where that's at
Delwath: ... 120-foot swim, 320 hit points.
Wellby: It's coming.
Delwath: AC 17, good wisdom and charisma saves, good strength.
Unknown: What, what room is Tim in in, um-
Delwath: Really good con, plus 10 con.
Wellby: I don't know exactly.
Unknown: Dining room?
Wellby: It's gonna be-
Delwath: Actually, in general, pretty good saves except INT saves are terrible.
Delwath: Wait, can you keep your metal boots?
Kenzo: I guess when we host big twists and stuff it's probably on the top floor.
DM: With a shape change, yes.
Kenzo: Maybe this is like the, uh-
Wellby: This is, this is like the family room.
Kenzo: Exactly. Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: This is our own-
DM: All right, I texted it to you.
DM: [gentle music] [keyboard clacking]
Seeker: Thank you. [keyboard clacking] All right, now I got it.
Unknown: [laughs] [objects thudding]
Wellby: Yeah. [keyboard clacking]
Seeker: Oh, it did acid damage. Oh, well.
Kenzo: [laughs] So this is the whole wanna make a slight change, you have to do all the moves.
Unknown: [laughs]
Wellby: Yes. [laughs] Exactly.
Wellby: This is the-
Unknown: Right. When the-
Wellby: ... why it's a bad idea to be your own rules actor
DM: ... true, true polymorph is a-